<cache>
    <entry id="1" title="The Journey." date="September 23rd, 2009">This is where the Journey begins, I guess. I&apos;m leaving Miami after I&apos;ve spent twenty-one years there. I&apos;m not looking for anything except happiness, something I do not have. I have no place I could go just now. No place I want to go. However, there&apos;s reasons to leave. There&apos;s always reasons to leave. If there weren&apos;t any, I could stay here.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I just want to travel around for a while, collecting impressions of the country I live in, see if I find a better place. One where I can enjoy life.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve quit my Job at 97.3 The Coast radio. It is hard for me to leave all of my life behind, move to a better place and start something new. They have told me it&apos;s said to see me going, that I can come back at any time  I want. But it isn&apos;t what I want, come back to my old life, although I liked the job. Maybe I can find something similar in future. I don&apos;t plan on coming back. Yet if I do, I have no assurance I will get my old job back...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I need something to work. I need to keep my mind busy,  I&apos;m trying not to think of it. That&apos;s the best thing I can do. I doubt I can ever forget the people I&apos;ve met... I have the collar still around my neck. I have the key to it. I don&apos;t want to lose that part of my life, it&apos;s something essential to me like my mind. Nobody should take it away, and I shouldn&apos;t even think about putting it away either. It&apos;s cold, but it tells me what I hoped for in my life. Happiness. Trust. Freedom? I don&apos;t want anyone to see it right now. I need to trust people before I can show them&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;... and I&apos;ve seen my trust getting abused so many times.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;With all the cash I could get, and a few donations from the people who still stick to me, I&apos;ve bought a mobile home, a Journey. It&apos;s all I need for a while. I don&apos;t want to stay in a place, I plan to move around. It&apos;s not large, but still enough for me. I&apos;m leaving all alone, and I can only look forward to my life getting better.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Happy 21st Birthday... Natalie?</entry>
    <entry id="2" title="Impressions." date="October 22nd, 2009">I&apos;ve seen many places. I&apos;ve seen many people, different people, different kind of people. Yet it&apos;s all just a far away dream to live a life I want to. I&apos;m broke, don&apos;t have much food and I&apos;m in the middle of the countryside. That&apos;s what comes to it, just a dull, open place where you can&apos;t get any support, no matter how much you need it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It feels different. Not welcome, rather I feel I&apos;m misplaced here. Feel this isn&apos;t the place I&apos;ve been looking for after all. I&apos;m alone, all alone. I don&apos;t want to go back. I&apos;d only go to the same places, seeing the same people again. I hate looking in their face, I hate having them around me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;m trying to get away from it all. I&apos;m ready to take pain up to a certain point. I&apos;ve been forced to cross this line. The bad part of it isn&apos;t that they&apos;ve put my body in a state where all I wanted is to get out of it... no matter how... even if I had to die. I didn&apos;t die. I had to take the pain, my body felt like tearing apart, I couldn&apos;t think, I couldn&apos;t recognize what was going on around me, I don&apos;t remember anything except the sole pain. I don&apos;t know if I deserved it, I don&apos;t ask that question. I&apos;m not the one to decide for what reason it happened. I couldn&apos;t sit straight for a couple of days, all I felt was the pain. But there&apos;s been moments... where I miss it... want to explore my body and see what&apos;s happening when I&apos;m pushed beyond my bounds, completely living in my own world with nothing around me. Only myself to focus on. It&apos;s all a part of my life... and the collar is a part I can&apos;t deny, can&apos;t get rid of on my own.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I have the key now. It&apos;s a strange feeling. I&apos;m carrying it with me, all the time, yet it feels so heavy. I don&apos;t want to have the key, yet there&apos;s nobody to give it to. I&apos;m alone. It doesn&apos;t feel good. My life changed, but right now... not to something good... but it&apos;s better. I want it to change something good... it&apos;s hard to, but I can only try. It&apos;s better than staying in Miami, but that&apos;s only one side... for the most part, it&apos;s been an enjoyable time. I miss it, a lot. I want to have someone who will help me getting back to my old lifestyle, just... doesn&apos;t abuse my trust. I want my old life back, the one I knew up to the days before it got worse... and before the day I was left in that alley. I&apos;ve tried this &quot;free&quot; way of life now and I can&apos;t see where it is better to what I just had three months ago... I want to start somewhere new... not with a different life, just with different people.</entry>
    <entry id="3" title="Los Santos." date="November 1st, 2009">I&apos;ve arrived in yet another town amongst the lots I&apos;ve seen - Los Santos. It&apos;s different than the places I&apos;ve seen before, each place is different, even unique. Just from looking at it, I can&apos;t tell if it&apos;s good or bad, I have to explore it. I have time, nobody is in my life, nobody will force me to come to a decision. It&apos;s all up to me. Do I even want to make a decision? For the most of the last four years, I didn&apos;t make the decisions. I didn&apos;t have to choose. I was given the way to live.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I was free to accept it or refuse it. I accepted it, for most of the time. It&apos;s not a final decision someone else has to make. You can always talk about it. I did sometimes, not often. I could accept it, live with it. I was given the option to deny it, but I had to face a punishment... That&apos;s not always bad, it can be good. But now, I&apos;m all on my own. I have decisions to make. I have to make decisions. Life ain&apos;t easy.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;For now, I&apos;ll stay around Los Santos for a bit. I&apos;m renting a room in the Jefferson Motel. It&apos;s nothing large, but enough. It&apos;s about the same size of the Journey, but then again completely different. It&apos;s a room to live in, not just a car to drive at day and sleep at night. I&apos;ll go look around the neighborhood, maybe finding a place I can settle in. I have to find a job as well, I can&apos;t just sit here and stare at the ceiling. I need to work for everything. I&apos;ll see what this place is like, what I can find.</entry>
    <entry id="4" title="A Place to call my Own." date="November 5th, 2009">It&apos;s not easy to make one. It&apos;s never easy. But I did, for once, make a decision I hope I can stay with. I can only see how it works out, if it wasn&apos;t a good decision... I&apos;ve got a slight problem. I&apos;ve traded in the Journey for a low class house in Jefferson. It&apos;s not the best there is in town, but there are worse places to own. It&apos;s next to some train tracks, and I can see the church when I&apos;m walking out my front door. I even got a lawn, and a driveway. Not that it is of any use, I don&apos;t have a car. I&apos;ll see who my neighbors are.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;There&apos;s a bar just a few blocks down, &apos;The Emerald Isle Tavern&apos;, I didn&apos;t try it yet but I&apos;ll go there soon. And a hospital just across the road from there, I wonder if there is any relation between those two.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve bought a few sweaters... It&apos;s getting colder, but that is not worrying me that much. It&apos;s rather to hide the collar below. I won&apos;t carry the key with me, I&apos;ll leave it at the house. Maybe it&apos;s dumb, but I need enjoy that feeling that I can&apos;t get out of it unless I get home again.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Right now, it&apos;s not looking all that bad, I can only hope it will get better. I&apos;ll try to find a couple of people I can trust... I need a couple of people to trust, I want to share my life with someone. Time will tell.</entry>
    <entry id="5" title="The News." date="November 6th, 2009">I&apos;ve been looking around to find a job, and I&apos;ve found something that looks interesting to me. It&apos;s similar to what I did back in Miami, just that it&apos;s not there.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I had a meeting with the CEO of San Andreas Network, Daniela Lane. She gave me a chance to work as anchor, which includes broadcasting news and the weather, and it looks like she isn&apos;t opposed to the idea of hosting some talk shows either. You&apos;ll hear me on the radio, but only know me as Natalie. I would rather not tell anyone my last name, I don&apos;t need anyone to know. Natalie is on a more personal level, and I prefer it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;As nobody except Daniela was around, I&apos;m still missing my introduction. All I received is the keys to the News Vans and Premiers, I still need my key card to enter the building without others. Since I don&apos;t know any others, haven&apos;t seen any others, I&apos;ll have to wait. I will try not to forget it, but I want to forget so many other things.</entry>
    <entry id="6" title="Nightlife." date="November 7th, 2009">I woke up at 20:00... I&apos;m trying to relax as much as possible. I don&apos;t have really much to do, I need the keycard before I can do a thing. Daniela called me to the SAN Tower, and I&apos;ve got my own key card for it. I&apos;m still missing an introduction to the tower itself and a few locations around town. I&apos;ll go ahead and figure out some on my own. But without ever being in this town, that&apos;s is easier said than done. I&apos;ve noticed a lot of people hanging out around the Gas Station at Idlewood, but I&apos;ve barely noticed anyone in Jefferson.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maybe it&apos;s just a little too late to wake up, to see people on the streets around here. I should stand up earlier, trying to talk with some of my neighbors. I could go to church as well. I guess it&apos;s a good place to get known to people, I suppose everyone around here is going there so if I want to meet people, I know where I need to go.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maybe not. I was just at some club called Tiger Bar. Besides the fact it was pretty empty, I was a little scared as well. My mind is still a mess, I can&apos;t deny that. I got a lot of good impressions for my time being here, but I believe without establishing a basic level of trust I couldn&apos;t open myself to others... I shouldn&apos;t open myself to others. I don&apos;t think I&apos;m that far and I really doubt a lot of people share my views.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve met someone from SAN, he&apos;s called Josh. He said he&apos;s been browsing on the company&apos;s website and seen me on there. I don&apos;t really want to be one of the famous people, I like to stay in the background and only talk to people over the radio. It gives me some distance and a way to open myself without actually showing myself. It is a difference between talking to people over the radio or phone and actually talking to them face to face. I don&apos;t like it, I&apos;m not great at it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Went to a bar in Jefferson, it&apos;s called &quot;The Emerald Isle Tavern&quot;. Met a couple of guys, but only one of them told me his name, it was Tom. Everyone seems to know each other, only I am new. I&apos;ll be here more often, so they&apos;ll recognize me as someone they can trust in, someone who is around and is always there to drink with. Speaking about drinking, I was pretty drunk. I have pretty much of a headache.</entry>
    <entry id="7" title="A Party." date="November 8th, 2009">Speaking about drinking, I still have a headache, suppose I was pretty drunk. Just a vodka here and there, trying to enjoy my time being there. It&apos;s not that much of a great feeling, but it&apos;s just to have a laugh with the guys and I eventually got over it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Still haven&apos;t got any introduction to my Job at SAN as a News Anchor, I do not know of anything. Since I couldn&apos;t really find someone at the tower, I&apos;ve been hanging out in the Emerald Isle again. They kicked us out for some minutes cause Mister Mayor came down here in this barely noticeable place, doing some business... god knows what. I know a couple of people&apos;s names now... One of them is called Robert, the one who owns the bar Jimmy C.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It was Daniela&apos;s Birthday, I didn&apos;t even know until they told me over Radio. I went to Josh&apos;s Tiger Club, and I found out she&apos;s apparently engaged with some Hans Vanderburg now, working for the Towing company. I&apos;ve danced with some other guy, Anthony Lloyd, kinda boring... didn&apos;t even want to drink anything. And some James guy, looking like a psycho, at least he went to drink some vodka with me. Now that sure is something, at least.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela drove me home. I felt kinda bad, because I didn&apos;t have anything for her birthday. I mixed a bit of tea for her, each cup with a shot of vodka, she drank four of them. I&apos;ve shown her the collar, and tried to introduce her what I&apos;m into... Handcuffed her behind her back, fingering and licking her to two forced orgasms on my couch. She seemed to enjoy it, even asked me if she could suck my fingers. She looked happy, but I wonder what she&apos;ll think about it tomorrow.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maybe it was just a little too weird for a birthday present. I&apos;ve told her she could stop it at any time just by saying so, but she did not. She&apos;s still sleeping in my bed right now, completely naked and exhausted I believe... and so will I, just with the collar on me. I only hope it won&apos;t have any bad consequences, I would hate to lose my job, or even be arrested for what I did.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Woke up in the middle of the night, got my pants and sweater on again. Walked out for a minute or two, trying to get fresh air. Emerald Isle is closed, so I decided to sleep there or rather, fell down there and was too lazy to get up. Robert joined me after a while, but didn&apos;t bring any vodka. He just went to watch me, and brought me home after some time.</entry>
    <entry id="8" title="Good Afternoon?" date="November 9th, 2009">It&apos;s late afternoon already. Daniela slept right next to me... and she woke me up. I was holding her, trying to make it a comfortable place for her, help her not to freak out about it. We were both in that bed, none of us had any clothes on, it&apos;s just the collar... She was pretty confused and didn&apos;t remember a thing of what happened yesterday. I&apos;ve given her shirt and skirt to her and hid her underwear just to see how she would react. Daniela didn&apos;t take it well, neither the fact she was naked nor that I didn&apos;t give her any underwear. I didn&apos;t offer her any of mine. I don&apos;t have a problem with running around naked in my house either, it doesn&apos;t make much of a difference. She saw me naked the day before, I saw her naked the day before, what would I need to hide... I told her what happened and she doesn&apos;t want to know of it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I believe she wants to explore her feelings... but at the same time is afraid of doing so. I know that kind of feeling, you have to decide whatever you&apos;ll listen to. Your mind, who tells you it was wrong... especially after the guy you love just proposed to you on the same day... or your body, who wants it and wants to have more of it, always more. I don&apos;t want to make her rush on a decision she will regret. I know what kind of choice I would love to see, but if she&apos;s not in for it, I&apos;ll accept that.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I have to accept that. I don&apos;t want to make the same kind of mistakes again. I have told people my decisions, and I lied to some people about my decisions. It only made the situation worse. I want her to think about it and ultimately tell me what she decided upon. There&apos;s no point in asking her to make a choice if she had no time to look at it. I&apos;ve tried to make fast decisions myself in the past, it ended up really wrong. Ever since that, I evaluate situations when I had some time to look at it, away from everything that influences my mind, away from the situation itself and I can think about what&apos;s right and what&apos;s wrong.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I only told her what happened in a neutral way, nothing from my own opinion. I know the life I chose, but I won&apos;t force her to go down the same way. I don&apos;t have the right to do so. I only want to be happy, I want her to be happy as well. I made some food for breakfast, she didn&apos;t eat anything. She should have, at least I was hungry and saw it necessary. I told her I got her to two orgasms, handcuffed on the back... And I told her she could have a break or stop it at any time just by saying so. She didn&apos;t do. After I told her she drank four cups of tea mixed with Vodka, she left the house.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I believe the situation is pretty messed up for her now. Ain&apos;t I evil? I&apos;m sorry.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She came back just a few minutes after. Told me what I did was illegal, but didn&apos;t really know what to do. She needs to calm down, there&apos;s nothing bad about it if both us it wanted it to happen and after all, I didn&apos;t force her to stay around. I don&apos;t know what&apos;s going to happen, she could report me to the police... or what I&apos;m personally more afraid of, fire me from SAN.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It never happened, and will never happen again... that&apos;s what she claimed, and if she does not want it to happen again I respect that. If she listens to what her mind thinks is good, there&apos;s no problem. I don&apos;t think she understands what her body wants. Either that or she refuses to accept it as part of herself, is ashamed of it, denies it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I told her about the collar, I want to be open about it. I want Daniela to open herself as well, I&apos;d hate her telling me a lie. All I wanted to do is showing her my lifestyle... the way I live, it&apos;s about trust in each-other, respect... enjoying and exploring your whole body... a life with no choice and no need to worry about your choices. You can&apos;t blame what you did on yourself if you had no responsibility, just act like you were told to... But at the same time, you don&apos;t need to listen to that, you can refuse to do what you&apos;re told, but you won&apos;t get away with it so easily. You still have a choice, but there&apos;s always the fear of what will happen if you do not agree. It&apos;s a different feeling if you&apos;re given a way, not freely choose between all opportunities. I prefer it that way. Not everyone does.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maybe Hans is the problem? She admitted she&apos;s done it in college before, but now she has someone to love. She enjoyed it back then... But now she can&apos;t... staying with Hans and not letting others coming close. If I was the reason why she didn&apos;t enjoy it... okay. I wanted to give her a pair of handcuffs for Hans, but she refused to take them.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela never wants to talk with me about this topic again.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I hope she&apos;ll come back.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;And then there&apos;s this Robert, met him in front of Emerald Isle. He scares me a little... He wants to be around me, watching me, just looking at me. I don&apos;t like it, I wouldn&apos;t really enjoy if he&apos;d notice the collar. It&apos;s covered by the sweater, but nothing more to hide it. If he&apos;d ever notice it, I had no idea on what to say. I know what it&apos;s for, I know I can get rid of it by just walking home and taking the key, yet it&apos;s a part of my life and I want to carry it around. I have no doubts about it, but on the other side I don&apos;t want random people I do not trust to know about it. Maybe not yet, maybe never. I&apos;m trying to be open to the people I know, telling them as much as possible. I&apos;m not really open to everyone else. It&apos;s my life I&apos;m trying to cover, because it is just different from anyone else&apos;s. And most people will not understand, can&apos;t understand the way I feel about it. I tried it once, and it&apos;s not working out. It&apos;s nothing people want to see. The people I call my friends acknowledge it... no, accept that it&apos;s a part of me. I made the mistake to trust all of them, and I&apos;ve seen the troubles caused by it. I&apos;m more careful now about whom I tell.</entry>
    <entry id="9" title="Busy." date="November 10th, 2009">I&apos;ve called Daniela over the radio, just to know when my introduction is going to be, I&apos;m now a few days down at SAN and it isn&apos;t looking like anyone&apos;s going to tell me about it. She called it a boring day with nothing happening, but refused my offer to spend some time together and come over to my place. Said &quot;some days are meant to be boring&quot;, then switched to &quot;I&apos;m tired&quot;. I do not quite believe that, but I suppose she is trying to avoid me. It&apos;s understandable after what happened but I would rather want an open discussion about it instead of her hiding from me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Does the latter work? I honestly don&apos;t know. Hiding probably does not, but you can run away from your problems. I&apos;m still dreaming those I left back in Miami will stay there, never catching up with my new life. I brought everything that I considered worthwhile with me, that is namely the collar. I left so much behind, people, things, everything I build up... just because I had problems I did not consider solvable. Maybe I shouldn&apos;t have ran away. Stay there. Talk. My opinion is different now, I&apos;ve had time to think about it. Running away didn&apos;t help me a lot, I had to throw my whole life away for a bunch of problems I wouldn&apos;t be able to solve alone. But at some point, the people I called friends were no people I could trust in any longer, I had nobody to trust in although I wanted somebody to talk to so bad... There&apos;s not always those two options. I couldn&apos;t talk to anyone, so I ran. Daniela hopefully has someone to talk to, she&apos;s engaged with Hans, she can talk to me as well. I won&apos;t bite her head off if I do not agree with her opinion.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I went to Emerald Isle again... drinking some Vodka, talking with people. I know someone else now, Mike. Not really someone, he lives with a friend and has no work. Tells me how he could live for a year without work. Maybe I could do so as well, I have never tried, but I&apos;d hate to have no work. I have to do something, just sitting on my couch all day long watching TV won&apos;t get me anywhere. I need to keep myself busy, I try to avoid too much free time at once.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I need to look forward.</entry>
    <entry id="10" title="A Note." date="November 10th, 2009">I went to the SAN building earlier than usual, with a few things in mind and a few things with me. I put a bunch of flowers, a pair of handcuffs and a note reading &quot;I love you.&quot; on her desk. Maybe it&apos;s one step too far. I&apos;ve been waiting. I&apos;m still waiting. I don&apos;t want to leave a bad impression though, if she decides against me I don&apos;t want her to keep me in mind as an evil person. I&apos;m not.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Took my laptop with me and was just reading through some websites while sitting in the lobby when Daniela called me. Telling me she&apos;s been thinking about this whole thing. I suggested her to come up and discuss it from face to face, not just over the phone. It&apos;s something important, I&apos;d rather want to look at her when talking about it. I have nothing to hide, not from Daniela... I want her to be a part of my life, and I want myself to be a part of her life... if she wants, at least. If not, I have to get over it. We&apos;ll see.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Went up to the office, and I&apos;m quite happy with how it went down. She admitted she can&apos;t be mad, and although she doesn&apos;t remember much of that night she told me she enjoyed it a lot. Now it&apos;s not really unexpected she&apos;s quite unsure on how to go on, she&apos;s quite confused. It&apos;s not really my choice. I want her to make a decision, and I want it to be the right one for her... I feel sorry for her, she told me everything she believed in just got twisted and she&apos;s unsure on wherever she still wants to marry Hans or not. At least she wanted to put the whole story up to now behind her, because I left her the choice to quit at any time... Daniela forgave me for what I did, if you can call it that way, and left me a note.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Thanks for letting me see my true feelings.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Didn&apos;t want to go out with me this time though. Maybe tomorrow, guess we&apos;ll see. But I can&apos;t deny I feel she took a step in the direction I want her to, and I hope she&apos;ll be happy with it. At least for this very moment, I feel I haven&apos;t done everything wrong.&#x0D;&#x0A;</entry>
    <entry id="11" title="Robert?" date="November 11th, 2009">I can&apos;t recall what happened yesterday after I&apos;ve talked to Daniela. Maybe I was just watching the stars, enjoying a lovely evening. Maybe something bad happened and I was just dumped there. No matter what, it&apos;s still too early, I&apos;m tired.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Robert, that guy living next to me, woke me up... I was apparently sleeping on the lawn in front of my house. Not that I mind it too much, my lawn is soft and feels comfortable, I go out there, just lay down and relax whenever I feel like doing so. But then again, I was tired, and all he said pretty much equals to &quot;make up your mind on what you&apos;re going to do&quot;. If you&apos;ve read a few entries up to now, you&apos;ll notice that&apos;s not what I want to be told, but oh well. Had some breakfast, alone. He didn&apos;t want to come over.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I still consider it a little odd, not weird. I&apos;m weird to most of the people, I hate to say that about others. It&apos;s just something that&apos;s about to freak me out a little, he&apos;s the only one who calls me by my full first name every few sentences... everyone else is just okay with &quot;Nat&quot; or &quot;Nats&quot;. Then again, as I was happy with breakfast and just went out for a walk, he told me &quot;Good Evening&quot; at half past six. Told me he&apos;s looking out for me... and for once, called me Jessica but doesn&apos;t know any Jessica? I really can&apos;t understand what&apos;s going on with him. He never had a girlfriend, he was never trying to get one, all it is comes down to looking out for me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Robert told me he has some interest in me... but he is only looking at what he can see, nothing beyond that. He doesn&apos;t know what my life is all about. I do not wish to tell him for now either. I don&apos;t want to see him again.</entry>
    <entry id="12" title="On Strike." date="November 11th, 2009">The Los Santos Emergency are on general strike. The newly appointed Deputy Chief of the LSES, Olivia Gunter fired and demoted a few ES members. I know something has to be done to show the rest of LSES are unhappy with this decision, and I do not believe a petition would change anything.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Just look at the world we live in. I&apos;ve seen countless petitions while browsing the Internet, I&apos;ve yet to see a petition who actually changed the mind of the people it&apos;s addressed to. There&apos;s doubts from my side most of the people who are addressed do not even acknowledge the existence of such the petition, and nevertheless read it. Now if nobody who has something to say in that matter reads them, you need to find other forms of protest which are actually acknowledged by the management. A general strike is one of them.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s still the ES, and that is the thing I have a hard time with. It&apos;s not just any company you do not need, it is an important part to contribute to everyone&apos;s health. Since those are not available, this city might as well end up in a mess.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Who is the reason for this strike? I&apos;ve mentioned earlier it&apos;s the kick of Deputy Chief Larry Thorne by the apparently new Deputy Chief Olivia Gunter. She worked for Mayor Joe Lautner as a bodyguard, in fact I&apos;ve seen her a couple of days ago with him in the Emerald Isle. Now that Lautner resigned, LSES Leader Charlie Baggett appointed her to a position that most of the employees of the Emergency Services looked up to, at least until now. A bodyguard becoming a part of LSES management? That is sure an impressive way of life, but it doesn&apos;t prove any qualification for that job at all.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Olivia Gunter called later, they&apos;ve resolved the issue, put Larry Thorne back in and she cleared up they&apos;re working for the safety of the public... and wants to address those issues internally, instead of letting everyone know of. That&apos;s not what I have in mind about an open government and informing us what tax money is spent on. A sudden collapse of the LSES would barely surprise me.</entry>
    <entry id="13" title="More Notes." date="November 11th, 2009">I drove back to the office and found Daniela outside. We talked about few things in our life, starting off with easy questions... She&apos;s living in some mansion in Vinewood together with Hans, just for the record. And I... only have that house in Jefferson, living all alone.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s time for a decision, but it&apos;s all about carefully approaching the topic, leaving her the chance on what way of life she&apos;ll go, even leaving her the chance on what role she wants to play in my life... and what&apos;s my role in hers. I don&apos;t think it&apos;s an issue that can be talked about so easily, and I doubt I could get as much influence on a decision just with talking to Daniela. Instead I wrote a couple of notes... Just simple ones first...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you trust me?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She does, or thinks she does. Trust doesn&apos;t equal trust, there&apos;s different kinds of trust. I can trust a couple of people with most of my life, but I do only trust a few of those with all of my life... maybe a few, maybe none. Few people know about it already, but Daniela is the only one in Los Santos who knows. I doubt she&apos;ll go out and tell everyone, I&apos;d be disappointed and sad.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;You know everything that happens is consensual, and you can stop it at any time you want just by saying so?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s a basic rule, one I will hate myself for if I ever violate it. One that led me to hate others who didn&apos;t follow it. It is quite simple, yet some people I knew ignored it, refused to listen to what I really wanted. Only one rule that needs to be enforced fully, one that you always have to keep in mind. It can get challenging to stick to at a point where you can&apos;t talk anymore, but when watching the other ones carefully there shouldn&apos;t arise any problem. If there&apos;s problems coming up, the worst thing you could do is run away or ignore them - at least in that situation. You always need to take care of it, and I want to feel I&apos;m safe with the people I trust, I want them to take care of me even when I&apos;m at a point I can&apos;t control myself anymore... You can&apos;t make it undone, but just being there, holding me gave me always a feeling I&apos;m safe and nothing bad will happen anymore... I can take a break from it if I want. I wanted it in almost every case.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I do not want to do anything which you do not agree to, and will not do anything that&apos;ll permanently change your life, unless you agree to it.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She acknowledges it, it&apos;s important to me as well. It&apos;s basically what I&apos;ve written above, just in different words that make it clear everything that happens might have an influence to the rest of your life. I want to live a similar way of life as I did in Miami... with Daniela... it can be bad, but there&apos;s so much in it being good. Loosing that would be none of my interests. Someone walked by, we went up to her office. It&apos;s a private matter, one that&apos;s just a thing of Daniela and me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you want to explore your feelings even if it hurts you?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Now this is a note referring to her note earlier, about how I showed her what true feelings she had... She&apos;s unsure about the exploring part, not about the fact I might hurt her. Again, nothing permanent unless she agrees to it. I only make up the questions to see how she reacts. It&apos;s not the easiest bunch of questions, you have to listen to what you want.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I can show you my life. It&apos;s up to you if you want to see it or not.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;My life, or what I believe is my life is based around the collar, around bondage and around pain. Those are the parts it is based upon and I do not want to miss any. I can&apos;t believe how my life would be without any of those. I will not force her into a decision, I&apos;ve tried to be as calm as possible. I&apos;m not speaking, I wouldn&apos;t know how I sound... unsure, calm, excited... maybe trying to convince her of a right choice. I do not want that. It&apos;s just some notes, notes can&apos;t speak but they can tell her what I have to say. Daniela wants to see my life.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;It&apos;s not easy sometimes. If you feel you&apos;re not up for the challenge, you can always go back. I won&apos;t be mad at you, I&apos;ll understand and respect your decision.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;This decision will change my life, it will change Daniela&apos;s life. I&apos;m aware both of us can take the step back and give up on it... I did take a step away, but I can&apos;t forget it. Maybe because the collar reminds me of what I&apos;ve done four years of my life... And I&apos;m just 21. I still want it, just not with the people I once thought I knew. There is a couple of points I&apos;m trying to get across, one of them is that I&apos;ll always respect on what she decides and that I won&apos;t force my will on her. It&apos;s important to understand that... people make mistakes, but there are some mistakes that should not be made.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela asked if it involves more than just us two. That&apos;s not anything that is really interesting for me, I wouldn&apos;t mind either. I want it to involve other people, someone I can rely on in every situation is always welcome. But it&apos;s not about me, this whole discussion is not about what I want. I know what I want. I&apos;m trying to figure out what Daniela wants, and I&apos;m in doubt wherever she knows herself.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you want it to involve other people?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;No. I was sure that would be the answer to a question like this, but on the other side she&apos;s engaged with a certain someone.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;... and Hans?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maybe. Now this is interesting, first she doesn&apos;t want anyone to know, but when I&apos;m asking about the person she loves... wait, does she? Let&apos;s just look at two of notes...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you love Hans?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you trust Hans?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She believes she trust and loves him, even more since they&apos;re engaged. I wrote a note and placed the one from above next to it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you trust anyone enough to tell them of this?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you trust Hans?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you need to trust somebody you love and whom you spend the rest of your life with?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Now this is something interesting, and one of the advantages of using notes. She doesn&apos;t want anyone to know... but at the same time fully trusts Hans and believes trust is one of the essential things you should have in a relationship. I can&apos;t deny that, but at the same time these notes are opposing each other. You can&apos;t trust Hans with everything, but at the same time trust him not enough to let him know. I think I&apos;ve got her to a point that is important, threw all of those notes off and placed a new one on the table.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you want anyone to know?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela should talk with Hans, should tell him about all of this and be open with it. I know it is hard to express your feelings sometimes, but I believe it is important you do. The only thing I ask for is not to deny it, but talk about it and make a decision you think is right. That doesn&apos;t imply I made the right decision, but it is a choice I once had and which I stick to. If you can&apos;t talk about it openly with the person you should fully trust, maybe you shouldn&apos;t trust that person at all. One of the things I expect of someone is that you can talk about with him about your feelings and what is going on in your mind. He doesn&apos;t need to understand it fully, but it helps a lot if he acknowledges it, accepts it to be a part of you.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;It&apos;s up to you. It&apos;s your choice, it&apos;s your life your current life.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Once again, I won&apos;t make a decision for her, but I believe she understands me a little to know her life will change if she wants to.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you trust me enough to give up control over a situation even if I make other decisions than you would in this situation, affecting both of us?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;No. Daniela doesn&apos;t trust me to that level, doesn&apos;t trust me fully. But who am I to her? Just someone random who happens to work for SAN. Who happens to spend a night with her, a night that wouldn&apos;t matter at all if she didn&apos;t want to. I&apos;m not the person to go around and talk bad about her if she made a decision I do not like. Different people make different decisions. Then again, giving up control over a situation isn&apos;t meant to be bad. I enjoy it most of the times, it&apos;s hard a few other times and it barely happens I regret it. I&apos;m not responsible for what&apos;s going on or what will happen based on that situation. I don&apos;t need to think of anything in the future or the past, I can fully focus on what is going on around me in that very instance. Daniela doesn&apos;t know that feeling, always decided on her own. She never let anyone else decide for her. Just about time to come back to an earlier note...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;... and Hans?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He never decided anything for Daniela, he gave her the choice or they made the decisions together... but okay, let&apos;s move on.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you think having choice is the definition of freedom?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Could you define freedom as having nothing to worry about?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;That&apos;s another pair of notes that looks nice next to each other. She agrees to both of them, but they&apos;re not really supporting each other. I know myself enough to tell her what I think...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I do not think having a choice is freedom.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;My second note made Daniela reconsider what she said, she would agree with me. I&apos;m not sure if she ever looked at it from my point of view, but it&apos;s something that I do not consider wrong. I wouldn&apos;t stick to it if it was wrong... Freedom, what is freedom? I ask her all those questions, leave her all those choices to think about it and make up her mind, but then I claim that&apos;s no freedom...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Would you rather want to have control or give all control away?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela rather wants to have all control. A question she didn&apos;t even think about, just answered without any hesitation. She thought a couple of minutes for the ones I asked before. Fair enough, that&apos;s the only question I&apos;ve been working towards to, to see how this will go on. It is not a question of wherever she accepts my way of life, it implies she does and asks her for the role she wants to take. She wants the control, but does she know the responsibility that comes with it? It would have surprised me if she made another choice, it&apos;s just somewhat selfish of people to think they should be given the control over others.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Having all control means you&apos;re fully responsible for whatever happens.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;That&apos;s about it. She is the only person I will rely on... I have the key with me, it is just a matter of her accepting it or not.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you think you can be trusted?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you think I should trust you?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She believes so... That&apos;s not too confident, but one of the things she need to gain out of all of this is self-confidence. It is something that&apos;ll help her. She wanted to ask me a question, but it&apos;s not really time for a question now. If she wants to take control over my life, she is free to do so. To be honest, I want her to do so. I trust her to a certain point, but it&apos;s now that I need to decide on wherever I&apos;m ready to fully trust her. I want to... I picked out an older note again.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I do not believe having the choice is freedom.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I trust you in everything you say.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s good she asks me why, but I&apos;m not here to answer it. I want to go on about all of this, and one of the requirements is complete trust.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I believe you can handle my trust and will not mis-use it.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you fully understand what an abuse of trust may bring with it?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She&apos;s fairly new to the topic and as such I do not think she&apos;ll start off with something heavy, something that&apos;ll present a risk to me. I have to introduce her to the whole topic, go further than just back on Monday. But on the same time, I want her to never abuse my trust...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;My death.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;You would be responsible for my death.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you understand this?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She promised me not to abuse my trust. I got her word, now all I can hope for is she&apos;ll keep to it. I put the key for the collar on the table. The key that ultimately limits my &apos;freedom&apos; as she&apos;d call it just yesterday. I have of course shown her the collar, it&apos;s always in its place, I can&apos;t ever get rid of it unless I use the key and I&apos;m about to give it away just now.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you want to take the key? The responsibility?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela wants to... and took the key. I can only clear up a few things, I guess.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I&apos;m bound to do everything you say. If I do not, you have to punish me You will punish me.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;It&apos;s a part of freedom for me. I don&apos;t want the choice, unless given by you. You need to show me where my bounds are, and what I&apos;m not allowed to do.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;I trust you.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s been sure an extensive discussion, and I feel pretty exhausted right now... but after all, I&apos;m happy. She asks me wherever I want to come down in the lounge or stay here. I point out it&apos;s not up to me and Daniela tells me to stay in her office, so I&apos;ll stay there. Just a few last notes, about what I think was wrong here...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you realize you should&apos;ve asked me those questions?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She guesses so...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;You probably would not have done that.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Do you think I would be here if I was unsure about my answers to them?&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;No. Though she&apos;s a bit confused now... and had to go, talk with Josh and gave me a day off. Before I went home, I just gave her one last note.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;If you&apos;re not sure about it - We can always talk.&quot;</entry>
    <entry id="14" title="An Hour with Josh." date="November 11th, 2009">I was at Tiger Club just a few days ago and eventually left with Daniela. But before that, I met Josh. We&apos;ve talked a few words and he introduced me to his girlfriend Danielle - and now this?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve picked him up from the airfield because he needed a ride and I just happened to be the only one not busy... and wanted to spend some time with me. Suggested we&apos;ll go to a diner, ate a salad... I&apos;m not really sure this will work out, he has a few girls in mind he has in mind to spend the rest of his life with, yet he has no plans to marry either of them. And he&apos;s going out with me, although he has a girlfriend? Seems a little weird.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He continued to show me his house, I mean... his house? There&apos;s a lot of places I could show any interest in, but his house is pretty small and not even cleaned up. Luckily Daniela passed by and walked in... Josh wasn&apos;t really amazed by that at all. I left with Daniela as he didn&apos;t want both of us around, but she just drove me home afterwards and left me there alone. I don&apos;t mind it all that much, it&apos;s been an interesting day that helped me a lot.</entry>
    <entry id="15" title="Six Flowers and a Note." date="November 12th, 2009">As I&apos;ve walked up in the SAN Tower today, there&apos;s been six flowers lovely arranged in the entrance area, together with a note in a handwriting that&apos;s unknown for me, no name given either.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;For Natalie, adore you.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I have no idea who sent it, but I doubt it&apos;s Daniela... and apart from that? I don&apos;t really know much people since I&apos;ve arrived in town and do not know of anyone who loves me. I&apos;ve put the flowers up in the office rooms.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Update: I found out who sent me the flowers. It&apos;s a guy who is working for SAN as Photographer, called Mohammad Johany. I fuckin&apos; hate him, he can&apos;t even speak English properly and he told me how romantic it is someone left those flowers - now I know why. There is no way I&apos;ll even consider to spend time with him, that simply won&apos;t happen.</entry>
    <entry id="16" title="Hans." date="November 12th, 2009">Emerald Isle again, same as every day. I recognize some faces by now, and people call me regular already. I&apos;m always drinking the same, a glass or two of Vodka, only sometimes a bit more.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans is the guy who I&apos;ve seen there for the first time, talked a bit with him. Told him I&apos;m working at SAN, he apparently knows a couple of people there. Josh for once, although only as Chief Editor and not as Intern. And Daniela, yeah...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He&apos;s the guy who is together with Daniela. She told me she will talk to Hans about this whole thing just today some time in the morning, and it&apos;s close to midnight... So I expected her to have it talked through with Hans, and since he didn&apos;t scream at me I thought it was okay. I have the note with me, the note I just got handed a couple of days ago. I know what it reads, looked at it...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Thanks for letting me see my true feelings.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;And Hans said he didn&apos;t talk to Daniela about me at all... not talking about work so much. And then he is sitting in front of me. I asked him for his number, I had to. I wanted to talk with him later, but I can forget that now.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Josh came in the bar as well, sat down between me and Hans to tell us he wants to sell Tiger Club... because there&apos;s nothing going on there. I don&apos;t know why he is here, why Hans is here, I can&apos;t believe all of this has to happen just now. I want to be open about it, but at the same time it&apos;s an awkward topic for the first time I&apos;m ever meeting Hans. I feel misplaced, once again. I don&apos;t want to talk about it, but I have to. It can get worse, but after all I didn&apos;t leave him with a lie.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He gave me a ride to my house... I roughly walk three minutes from my home to Emerald Isle, but it felt like it took hours in his car. He told me it&apos;ll be alright, I just shouldn&apos;t work so much. But work isn&apos;t the problem, Daniela isn&apos;t the problem... the note is the problem, and what&apos;s written on it. I had to show Hans the note, it&apos;s about someone he loves, someone who loves him. I told him when she gave it to me... the day after her birthday. I know Hans proposed to her on that day. I didn&apos;t tell him what happened, what led her to write the note.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I was scared. He was pretty calm and just confused... scared me even more. If he was angry about it, I would&apos;ve understood it. If he raged about it, I would&apos;ve understood it. He&apos;s not the kind of guy who is getting angry so easily. But then... disappointed in Daniela because she didn&apos;t tell him the truth.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I thought they talked about it already. They didn&apos;t. I told him about it, gave him the note. I don&apos;t want him to live without knowing what is going on with the people close to him, I want to be honest. I was... I think I&apos;ve screwed it up.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I can&apos;t imagine a worse first meeting.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I went to Tiger Club afterwards to see Daniela, to tell her about my conversation with Hans. I really felt I did something wrong... but she wasn&apos;t mad and told me it is going to be alright. I can only believe in her words, and hope it&apos;ll end up that way. I don&apos;t question what she said.</entry>
    <entry id="17" title="Nobody wants my Life." date="November 13th, 2009">Daniela called me for a meeting at SAN... After everything that happened, it&apos;s probably all about me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I was just sitting in their tower and researching some stuff about the election and candidates, so I&apos;ve had nothing better to do either way.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She talked to Hans. He forgives Daniela for what she has done to him... with me... But Daniela thought about it, and thinks it&apos;s not fair to Hans to have the key in her possession... It&apos;s not Hans choice, it&apos;s her own and she feels bad about it... I don&apos;t want the key back, not at all.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The last thing Daniela decides to do with the key is... to release the collar... the worst thing that ever happened to me since I moved in this town... I&apos;ve spent four years on building my life. It was ruined in Miami. I came here and wanted things to be different... they are different, but not in a way I would ever want them to be.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I wanted Daniela to decide upon her own, I wanted to leave her the choice. She could drop out at any time, but I don&apos;t want it myself, I don&apos;t want it to be like this. The collar is just something in my life I can stick to, I thought something that&apos;d never go away... it makes me feel safe, there is something that I have apart from everything going on outside, may it be good or bad. When I looked inside at least, it gave me a feeling of happiness that wouldn&apos;t go away... Now that she took the collar off, I can&apos;t enjoy it...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I have SAN, Daniela and Josh? As friends... they said they&apos;ll never leave me... never forget me... but that&apos;s not what I want... that doesn&apos;t make me happy... I thought I found a way to be happy, a person to be happy with - Daniela... now she released the collar, put it in my hands.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;A chance to let them show me that I can have the world as what I make it? What do I even want the world to be? I wanted it to be a place where I can be free and happy... I had that just until this moment, and now all of it is taken away... My choice? I know the choice I wanted... but I respect her choice, I don&apos;t want to leave a bad impression.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve looked at what&apos;s engraved on the inside, what I wanted there... I haven&apos;t done so in four years, never had the chance to... What about my life? What is left except to cry? It&apos;s not my life anymore... I don&apos;t have a purpose in my life, I don&apos;t have anyone... Nobody wants my Life, not even I do.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve said Good Bye to Daniela. I don&apos;t know where I&apos;ll go, but I won&apos;t see Daniela again, SAN again. I don&apos;t want to see it again, I need to step away from all of this.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What is there left to say? Why would I want to live here, with a life I don&apos;t want to have, don&apos;t even want to be my own? I came here, and I have no reason to stay. Daniela is telling me it&apos;s alright... but that&apos;s just not true. Nothing is alright for me, but maybe it is for her. She&apos;ll marry Hans and won&apos;t have to worry about me no more. I&apos;ll just forget about all of this, won&apos;t get involved at all. I listened to what my body told me is right, not what my mind told me. I knew Daniela was engaged, and it all started on her birthday party, I knew it couldn&apos;t end up right. I&apos;ve looked at what&apos;s engraved on the collar for the first time in four years. I never got the chance to look at it... I didn&apos;t want to either.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;Go by your instinct, get down the real thing. She&apos;s no lie, never leads you wrong.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;There&apos;s no place for me, I&apos;ve tried to find it... I wanted to find it... I believe I found it, but I was wrong. I don&apos;t want to see either Hans or Daniela like this. I&apos;ve caused so much trouble already and even though they claim I&apos;m welcome as friend, I don&apos;t want to make it even worse. I tried to get my life to something better, and when I thought I had someone to trust and to believe in...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I wanted to base my life off something, something that just came from her heart, something I believe she really meant it the way she wrote it. But there&apos;s no place to allow such weakness, she came to think of it and... decided against it. She doesn&apos;t want this, not with her mind... I&apos;m pretty sure she decided against what she really wanted, but I accept it, I don&apos;t question it. I can&apos;t make her change her mind if she does not what to.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What&apos;s all this worth? I believed in something, and that&apos;s all just ruined. I based my life off my believes... of freedom and whatnot... that nobody wants to see or even know about. Hans just has the definition of freedom everyone has... nobody has mine. I&apos;ll just leave... this is no place for me to live in, or even be in. I don&apos;t want to have the choice in my life, I want to enjoy it and I want everyone to enjoy theirs.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;My definition of freedom doesn&apos;t exist, that&apos;s what I&apos;ve just learned. I&apos;ll stay out of their ways, hope they&apos;ll be happy without me... I knew it had to end like this, didn&apos;t want to know of it though. I gave Hans a last note for Daniela...&#x0D;&#x0A;I didn&apos;t want this to happen, but it&apos;s nothing unexpected... Being there just makes it harder for me to forget about you... and I believe it&apos;s in your and Hans&apos; interest to not see me around so often. I won&apos;t come back here,&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ll leave SAN and I&apos;ll leave you. I&apos;m thankful for meeting you, but it wasn&apos;t meant to last. Farewell, and enjoy our time with Hans.&#x0D;&#x0A;- Natalie.&#x0D;&#x0A;PS: We can always talk, but if you won&apos;t change your mind, I guess I won&apos;t change mine either. 37965.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I left... I just went back home, with nothing apart from that. I have the collar, but in my hands... I have the key I hate so much. I want someone to have it, and the collar around my neck as well. Daniela just took it off in an instance, taking away everything I believed in. What is there more than to look at it now, think of what my life could&apos;ve been and leaving this place... Maybe to another town, maybe forever.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s not possible for me to be happy. Nowhere, never.</entry>
    <entry id="18" title="A Meeting." date="November 13th, 2009">I went home with nothing. I have the collar and the key again, but not around my neck. Daniela took it off... I&apos;ve just spent hours looking at it...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans and Daniela came over in the evening... to my place in Jefferson... to talk about me, I guess. Told them I got the collar four years ago in Miami, the words I believed in engraved... I believed in them four years, even longer than that... but after today, it feels like nobody thinks like that. I don&apos;t believe in them anymore. I don&apos;t know what to believe in at all.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Their views on this world are different than mine yet they want to show me what they believe in... their freedom, their happiness. I can only tell them what&apos;s my views on that, they let me talk about it...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;There&apos;s a reason for Hans and Daniela coming here. Daniela wants me to stay in SAN but has no idea how to. I know what could be done... and Hans placed the collar around my neck, saying it&apos;s a part of me I shouldn&apos;t give up. Daniela took the key again. I can&apos;t express how happy I am, I just am, it&apos;s a moment in my life beyond a point where I believe it... One thing I wanted so much and now it just happened. It&apos;s something I wanted since I met Daniela, something I wanted even more since she took the collar off. I don&apos;t want their life too much, but after all, they can accept my life and the collar as a part of it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela left later, something to do with an Army base in San Fierro. I&apos;ve spoken to Hans afterwards, told him I can&apos;t take the collar off without the key Daniela has now... that I trust her to do the right thing in the best interest for both of us. I don&apos;t have to worry about what happens, why it happens and what will be the result of it... I can relax and enjoy the situation, it&apos;ll always remind me of my life they both accepted by now. I won&apos;t forget it, loose focus on it, I know my place and my friends... I always have something, no someone to believe and trust in, no matter what happens. It can be hard at times, challenging, but that&apos;s nothing bad. It&apos;s a part of me and my life.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela told Hans what happened on the day after her birthday, about my offer... to let Hans join in... and he agreed with it if she did. I&apos;m okay with that, I don&apos;t mind and if both of them agree, that&apos;s fine.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans left, said it&apos;s been a confusing day. I can only support that statement, even more it&apos;s been a hell of a day... A day that broke my life apart and put me back in the place I wanted to be in, even more... they&apos;re both okay with me.</entry>
    <entry id="19" title="Countryside." date="November 13th, 2009">Josh called in over radio later about the new house he bought. I went there with him, some of his friends and Daniela. I&apos;ve apologized for the trouble I&apos;ve caused her, massaged her neck... I just wanted to do something good to her after what happened. And I&apos;m glad it turned out this way. If today has shown me one thing, then that I can&apos;t be happy without Daniela, the collar or my life as it is now.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve asked her if there was anything she wants, anything I could do for her. All she thinks of is some farm in the country. We went there later, it&apos;s pretty huge and has a large field attached to it. The owner might not sell it, but the price shouldn&apos;t be a problem.  I&apos;d do anything to make Daniela happy. I know I don&apos;t have to, but I love her and want to. Money shouldn&apos;t be a problem, not something that should make her worry. She brought so much happiness in my life and I want her to be happy as well.</entry>
    <entry id="20" title="Office Work." date="November 14th, 2009">I was a little bored, so I&apos;ve decided to call our SAN Pilot, Zoey Edwards, to drop me off at the roof of the Impound lot of Best&apos;s Towing and Recovery. Well aware of the fact Hans is the CEO of that company, I went in with the single intention to see Hans. With that in mind, I&apos;ve entered their building, walked into Hans&apos; office and cuffed myself behind my back to his table... Just waiting for him to come there.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He eventually came. I told Hans I&apos;m here to see how he works and that I&apos;ve been getting in over the roof, no one really let me in. Wondered what this is... well, I&apos;m not sure what it is? Me breaking into his office to have some fun... or to look at what he&apos;s doing there? I have the key for those handcuffs with me. Not in my hands, but at least on the table so it&apos;d be Hans&apos; option to do whatever he wants. He put them in front of my feet, I could&apos;ve freed myself if that&apos;d be what I desired in that situation. Needless to say, it isn&apos;t. I&apos;ve kicked the keys away, put them in a place unable for me to reach.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans said he has to punish me... for the thing that note was about. Massaging me... Asking me if I still want to go on... What does he expect me to say? There&apos;s nothing much I can do, it&apos;s all up to Hans. Undressed me. Played a bit with me, moving the key for the handcuffs around on my body. It&apos;s a strange feeling, some part of me wants to be free again, but for the most of it I don&apos;t want to. But I really like this, if that&apos;s a punishment then it&apos;s one I want more of.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He put the key in the lock, was about to unlock the cuffs, that&apos;s really the  last thing I want to... he blindfolds me and removes them afterwards... He&apos;s licking me... fucking me... two orgasms... Calls this a punishment, something I deserved. I was laying down there, pretty much unable to do anything, just breathing. He took me home. I could barely stay on my feet and fell into my bed, thinking about the whole thing, sleeping.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s amazing how fast this whole thing with Daniela and Hans changed from only me wanting it, Daniela and now Hans joining in and I love it.</entry>
    <entry id="21" title="A Farm out there." date="November 14th, 2009">I&apos;ve been doing some actual work later. Called the owner of the Farm Daniela would like to own, it&apos;s just $300,000. Despite the fact I&apos;ve collected some cash now, I couldn&apos;t see any better way to spend it on if not to make Daniela happy. There&apos;s nothing I wouldn&apos;t do to make her happy, nothing. It&apos;s been quite some trouble to get everything that was in the farm out, a load of assault weapons... pretty weird, I&apos;d expect some hunting rifles as that&apos;s what you need on a farm the most. Then a lot of cars... Mr. Harm, who owned the ranch, rented out a room to someone else... I&apos;ve waited a few hours for him to appear and he finally got his stuff out. But after all, that&apos;s nothing I wouldn&apos;t have done.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Let&apos;s see what Daniela thinks of the Farm now she owns it.</entry>
    <entry id="22" title="Don&apos;t play with food?" date="November 15th, 2009">We have a new Office Tower. We&apos;ve moved from between Idlewood Gas and Pershing Square, the area with most traffic in town, most car crashes as well I guess, to our new location in Rodeo. Just the highest tower in Rodeo, not too far away from the Second Precinct of the Los Santos Police Department. There&apos;s barely any traffic around here, even more you always get a nice view on the beach.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve met Daniela outside and talked a bit with her... Asked her if she wears some underwear, she looked rather shocked. I can&apos;t understand that from my point of view, I&apos;m not really used to underwear. I hate to wear clothes, and I wouldn&apos;t mind if everyone would walk around naked. It just limits you quite a bit but it&apos;s one of the things natural in our society. There&apos;s no way to avoid it. It won&apos;t hurt her, I won&apos;t hurt her. There&apos;s nothing bad that can happen, is there? Maybe she&apos;s afraid of others seeing it, others looking up her skirt but then... it&apos;s the most natural to not wear any clothes. What would you do to anyone not wearing underwear? Invite them to your home for a cup of hot coffee? She put them off, but it didn&apos;t take a minute for her to take them out of the dirt and put them back on despite me telling her not to do that.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She didn&apos;t listen, how dare. All I can do is keep it in mind, she&apos;s in a position to easily do anything she wants, she can just walk away. You can&apos;t take revenge on someone who has a chance to run away. That&apos;d be weird, but if not now it&apos;ll get to her later. Nothing to change her mind, but it&apos;s been fun at least, her face was pretty red. She&apos;s listening to everything I say to her. But there&apos;s apparently a difference between listening and doing, she&apos;s not comfortable with doing everything. That&apos;s understandable but something that can be changed. She doesn&apos;t want to relax and just enjoy the situation... not that she&apos;d regret it, although I can never be sure. But if you don&apos;t try, you can never figure out. She doesn&apos;t want to do it just in front of her office... okay, she drove me to her home.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Is there anything to fear? I&apos;m here for that reason, there&apos;s nothing she should worry about. Daniela is afraid something bad might happen... You can never exclude that possibility, but I&apos;m here to make sure she&apos;s alright, she can take it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;When we finally arrived at her mansion, I was quite a bit amazed. It&apos;s pretty large, there&apos;s a nice view from the balcony and my place in Jefferson is nothing compared to it. After knowing Hans and Daniela for a couple of days, I thought it&apos;s finally time to eat something together, the more interesting the meal is, the better. For that reason, I&apos;ve brought a box with me with a bit of the usual stuff in. There&apos;s a nice round glass table on her Balcony and it&apos;s looking quite good to test it out. The worst thing that can happen is probably for it to break through... it looks solid, but you never know unless you try out. And the way to try out would be to put Daniela on it and see if it can take her with her back on the table, looking up to me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;How does this help to find out what&apos;s in the box? Now for one thing, I know what&apos;s in the box, only Daniela doesn&apos;t. But she&apos;s laying on the table and that&apos;s at least a good start to figure exactly that out. Well, for once it&apos;s handcuffs. That&apos;s not quite unexpected looking at my hobby, she could&apos;ve guessed it without problems. It doesn&apos;t really matter though, I&apos;ve cuffed each of her arms and legs to one of the table legs, it&apos;s quite useful for a round table with four legs. Daniela minds me kissing her quite a bit, but I told her Hans wants to join in and I&apos;ve agreed to it. Daniela agreed to it before as well, so there&apos;s nothing wrong with it really. So far, the table is doing quite well, it&apos;s still holding her and even more, restricting her in her movement. She can&apos;t really do much against me rubbing her tights and I doubt she would do anything if she was free.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve taken a piece of cloth out to play around with it, and all she guesses what it&apos;s for is for blindfolding her. But an object doesn&apos;t only have one purpose, it&apos;d be wrong to say that. The table we&apos;ve been talking about is usually to serve food on it and now I&apos;m probably the first one to have Daniela laying on it with no panties. Back to the piece of cloth, I could use it to blindfold her, but I could also rub her vagina with it... it&apos;s all a piece of cloth, it doesn&apos;t tell me what to do with it, I can do what I want. And Daniela couldn&apos;t even run away, regardless of whatever I&apos;m doing. I could get a boo and read it, no matter how long I take I would be the one who could stand up at any time. Daniela just has to wait for someone else to release her. I blindfolded her shortly afterwards though.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans is the person Daniela is engaged to, the person she wants to marry and the person who wants to join the fun. It seemed only natural to invite him, to call him to join our meal. I called him, and he came over shortly after. I looked around in the kitchen and took some food with me out on a tray and placed it on a chair. Daniela is a bit hungry already, but that&apos;s barely a problem now.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;For once, a skirt, shirt and bra are the only clothes Daniela has still on, but I figured that&apos;d be a bit limiting. I&apos;ve asked Hans to take them off, I don&apos;t want to do all alone... I&apos;m the one who brought those idea, yet I would love to see myself in Daniela&apos;s position at the meal. I&apos;m comfortable with controlling her, but it&apos;s not the thing I want most. I didn&apos;t gave her the key for no reason, I want her... to control me. Only time can tell and I hope she&apos;s at some point ready for it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans didn&apos;t rip the shirt off but uncuffed her to do it... Cuffed her again and fed her a bit, ate some of the food. Stuck some food inside her. I would say she liked it pretty much, enjoyed it, wanted more... but I didn&apos;t give her more, left her there, just occasionally put some food in her, massaging her... Left much of a mess on her body, but there&apos;s no problem licking it clean, is there? Hans helped me quite a bit, but there&apos;s still this thing from the SAN tower left... she refused to follow my orders. If I tell her to do something, she has to do it... That&apos;s the least thing I expect. I&apos;ve slapped her a few times on her vagina, kissed her in between so she wouldn&apos;t be so loud.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela decides? It&apos;s easy... She decides as long as she wants to. If she gives up the control over a situation, gives it to someone else, there&apos;s nothing she can decide anymore. It&apos;s up to me, Hans or whoever is around to tell her what to do and of course we want her to listen to us. That&apos;s something to learn... follow the orders. It hurts. It has to hurt, so she will learn it and won&apos;t make the same mistake again. Daniela believes she&apos;ll learn it some other way, that the thing with pain is not how she works... but that&apos;s not true. She ain&apos;t having her fingers on the hot oven all day long, it hurts so she takes them off. Yet with this approach, she won&apos;t do it again or be punished again... and she doesn&apos;t seem to like it. Pain is a part of my life and I think she&apos;s accepting it as part of her life as well. She didn&apos;t tell me to stop it. That&apos;s the other option, the way out, to stop it all at once with no questions asked.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Who am I to tell her? I only look down at her, spread and cuffed to the table and I would need to be pretty blind to not see her enjoying it. She&apos;s even asking for more, not of the pain of course. She wants to have all control but this situation is quite good for her.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Will she refuse to listen to my orders again? She hopes not. I don&apos;t want to hurt her if it&apos;s not necessary, but at times it&apos;s needed to aid her in learning. I&apos;ve put my flat hand on her vagina again, asking if I should slap it a few more times since she didn&apos;t give me a final answer. She&apos;s afraid of the pain, doesn&apos;t want it and finally tells me she&apos;ll listen.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I only went her for a meal, and now Hans is on the table with Daniela and I wouldn&apos;t say she&apos;s too far away from an orgasm. I got some cream for Hans, he wants to have a desert. Some cream on Daniela&apos;s body to lick off and then he moved in her...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I was about to leave, yet Hans called me back, put me on a chair and cuffed me behind my back. He went ahead and uncuffed Daniela, telling her to &quot;pleasure&quot; her guest. She took my clothes off, pressed her mouth again mine and kept french kissing me while Hans played with a vibrator inside me. I couldn&apos;t breathe through my mouth really, I was just there sweating being forced to an orgasm, Daniela massaging my breast with one hand, Hans licking the other one.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;&quot;That&apos;s how we treat guests like you.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans moved away, leaving the vibrator still in place... he moved behind Daniela and helped her feeling good while she was still kissing me... It was quite a lot to take, another orgasm for me, still barely able to breathe. A simple meal, and now this. He uncuffed me eventually, they&apos;ve pulled me up and we walked around the house... they&apos;ve got a present for me, a car... I&apos;ve just said once I had no car, now I have an Euros, it&apos;s great. We&apos;ve walked inside, I had a bath. It&apos;s great here with both of them. I can&apos;t be thankful enough to have this as my life...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I make Daniela happy... and Hans is happy with it as well... Hans promised me to stop whenever I want that, if I want that.  That&apos;s quite a lot to me, as it means I can trust him... and then again, I&apos;ve told him he can punish me if I did something wrong. Like the &quot;punishment&quot; in the office which makes me want to do it again so I can get more of that kind. He enjoys it... and so do I.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He put me in a bed for me to sleep. It&apos;s been an interesting day but exhausting as well.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What&apos;s the happiest day in my life so far? The day I&apos;ll never forget... I know what is. Just a couple of days ago... After they broke my life apart, Hans and Daniela came over to my place to... discuss all of this... about me, with me. And they put the collar back around my neck, Daniela took the key and still has it. It&apos;s not an ultimate form of control, I can still act on my own, just as I did today. But once I&apos;m told otherwise, I know I&apos;ll be punished if I go against that. Just the same happened to Daniela today. It&apos;s good if you&apos;re afraid of punishment. I am, because they haven&apos;t done anything bad to me so far and I really wouldn&apos;t know what either of them is capable of.</entry>
    <entry id="23" title="Interview." date="November 15th, 2009">Had an Interview with Malcolm Everett, this guy from the Los Santos City Council. He presented his stuff, why people should vote for him and all that usual stuff. He&apos;s more of a choice than Roger Aegelmaere who is a German Communist with a lack of English, while Maccer Davidson wants to legalize some drugs... At all, not much to choose from, but it&apos;s clear who the best choice is. The interview was interrupted by a few clowns pretending they&apos;re dogs, not really something usual but after all, Hans managed to command them around well enough. Wonder if he&apos;s getting used to giving orders by now. It really much looked like it, and although it was a little troublesome at first, we&apos;ve completed the interview and had a few callers asking questions as well.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve met with Daniela, Hans, Josh at the Farm later, Daniela wanting to show off it as their new country home. Turned out it wasn&apos;t all that great, Hans has been kidnapped and brought there once for a month, two years ago. He isn&apos;t much of a fan. Daniela went to drive Quads with Josh while Hans told me more details... It&apos;s pretty terrifying to see this kind of things happening. Not a kidnapping or being locked in a place for a month, that could turn out interesting. But that it&apos;s done without agreement or a chance to get out, that&apos;s nothing what I&apos;d ever want to happen to me. Seems I&apos;m missing quite much on the kidnappings though, Daniela has been kidnapped ten times, Hans that one time and I haven&apos;t been ever since I came here. I was tired, Hans drove me home while Josh and Daniela went to Blueberry, buying equipment for the farm.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Nobody forces Hans to come here though, if he doesn&apos;t want nobody can help it. It&apos;s understandable at least. I hope it&apos;ll go away... I hope.</entry>
    <entry id="24" title="Aegelmaere." date="November 16th, 2009">Sometimes my job is just bad luck, and this was one of the days. Woke up, Hans came over and I had to Interview Mr. Roger Aegelmaere who contacted me every five minutes for an interview and with all there is to it, he was annoying. What are his goals despite the usual shit promised by politicians, anything that hasn&apos;t been brought up before? Make Best&apos;s Towing and Recovery a government company is surely one of those ideas. Now you can surely imagine Hans as the one leading the Towing company sitting next to the guy who wants exactly that in government possession. I don&apos;t recall much of this interview but Hans falling off the chair and laughing once he found out Mr. Aegelmaere still works for him - and with all due respect, that&apos;s understandable and explains even more why BT&amp;amp;R and not any other company. Socialism Party, the fuck is that you might wonder... Don&apos;t ask me - I didn&apos;t get anything out of it besides the fact he&apos;s a moron who can&apos;t speak English. If that&apos;s all there is to it, you shouldn&apos;t candidate for Mayor and have even less people voting for you.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I drove with Hans to his place and asked him if he wanted to try out the cuffs. He cuffed himself while I stripped myself naked, things just happened as he sat in that chair... sucked a bit though, he kept massaging my breasts and whatnot with his feet and I would lie to say I didn&apos;t like it. It sure is something different to see Hans who&apos;s usually in charge like this but I doubt it&apos;s his thing to be cuffed himself and have others to do what he wants. It&apos;s been fun while it lasted, didn&apos;t really have much time though.</entry>
    <entry id="25" title="Moving In." date="November 18th, 2009">I can&apos;t sleep anymore, not as long. I&apos;ve spent ages in bed but only slept two or three hours. It sucks, I need sleep... I&apos;m tired. I don&apos;t want to sleep because I know what I dream of. I&apos;m waking up when I dream of it. I&apos;m having just that thing in my dreams for a couple of days. It&apos;s annoying and I&apos;m afraid it might happen again... If it does I&apos;m lost. If I meet the same people again I&apos;m lost. I can&apos;t keep dreaming of Miami all the time, it&apos;s giving me a headache nowadays even when I only hear that word.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans called me, didn&apos;t really interrupt me from sleeping though. I was just laying in my bed trying to sleep because I&apos;m tired... not to sleep because I know what I&apos;ll dream of. They&apos;re moving to 1 Rich Street. They. Hans and Daniela. They. Not me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans wanted to show me the house and picked me up. Three hours of sleep aren&apos;t healthy, I wasn&apos;t really in much of a great mood. It&apos;s an even larger mansion with an indoor swimming pool, a gym, a bar, a recording studio, rooms to relax, an office, five bed rooms... another pool outside, a helipad... with something on it. I wasn&apos;t asked to move in, he asked me when I&apos;ll move in... I asked him how much time I have, two hours. Enough to do it, I mean after all I barely have anything to bring here, I wouldn&apos;t need days. Hans helped me and I fell into the bed, yet again trying to sleep. Needless to say I&apos;ve had problems with it... At least I have people around me now, living with people I love.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;We had a meeting in SAN later, discussing on our course for the next time. There&apos;s commission for anything you do beyond your quota... and I&apos;m apparently Lead Anchor now with a $700 wage. I&apos;m making too much already, it won&apos;t get better.</entry>
    <entry id="26" title="Josh." date="November 18th, 2009">Went down to Emerald Isle again, drinking a bit before I go to bed, talking to Josh. He came there as well... it&apos;s the only place I drink... and offered to drive me home. I&apos;m having some kind of visitor in my house in Jefferson, not really a place I would go to. I&apos;m already living in Hans&apos; and Daniela&apos;s place though, so it&apos;s not much of a hassle to decide on where we should head to... and where we went to. It&apos;s a huge place, not that I paid for it though.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I know he has a girlfriend, he said she&apos;s out of town, Las Venturas maybe... technically free with no chance to be seen by her when he&apos;s together with other people... like me. Guess Hans likes me around, he asked me to move in told me to move in just today. Though with Daniela... He loves Daniela, might be a little awkward when I&apos;m around his place all the time. Could it be more awkward than it is now?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maybe I should put a bar in my room... I&apos;m a reasonable drinker, I didn&apos;t drink myself to death even once. Josh calls his girlfriend more an opportunity, she is not someone he loves. That&apos;s quite different from Daniela, I won&apos;t even leave her alone even if I hated her. Not something quite easy to understand, I guess. Can&apos;t say Hans minds me around, I&apos;m not much of a problem for him. If they both wouldn&apos;t like me at least, I wouldn&apos;t live here.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Went few rooms down to the bar with Josh, I took another vodka, he took a beer.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I wouldn&apos;t be here without them... but even if I hated them right now, the key leaves me not much of a choice but to stay, that&apos;s pretty strange. Josh is asking quite a bit about my relationship... asks me if I&apos;m in love with Daniela Lane... there&apos;s no reason to deny it, he&apos;s been wondering about that ever since he came here... He says it&apos;s cute that I have someone to love who loves me as well, wants to keep me around... and someone I trust. If he&apos;d say he loves Daniela, I doubt she&apos;d be interested... Josh&apos;s saying it&apos;s hard to talk with her, he doesn&apos;t really know her that well as she&apos;s protective of herself. But I can&apos;t say it&apos;s easy to convince someone to show their true feelings especially with what our relationship is. I understand if she isn&apos;t open about it, but is your life something you should hide? Something to be ashamed of if it just feels so good?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Lesbian? Bisexual? That&apos;s nothing I want to be called like, I&apos;m just a normal person and enjoy spending time with both Hans and Daniela. It can be fun, it can be damn hard at times... Freedom is not about having a choice, it&apos;s to have nothing to worry about for me. If I&apos;m submissive, I have certain choices taken away and thus they&apos;re not a part of what I can change. It&apos;s not my goal to think about what would have happened if I took another path, there are no other paths. Are we destined by god to fuck shit up then think about it? That doesn&apos;t sound like the way I want it to be. Maybe Josh thinks that way, I don&apos;t.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;That&apos;s why I&apos;m still with Hans and Daniela. Not because they tell me everything I have to do but because there are situations I can fully enjoy, where I do not have to think about the consequences or where I couldn&apos;t even change it if I wanted to. There&apos;s not a lot of people to understand me... Josh does, says it&apos;s all in what you believe, the way you feel yourself free.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;There&apos;s a difference between freedom of body and freedom of mind. You need to restrict your body&apos;s freedom to extend my mind&apos;s freedom, fully give away control over a situation and just watch it evolve around me without having any influence at all.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;My life before I moved to San Andreas has been great at times, horrifying at times. I&apos;ve enjoyed it as much as I never wanted stuff to end sometimes. I&apos;ve been put in situations where I wanted to die. There are bad days for everyone but some of them are just worse. It&apos;s not something I want to talk about with Josh whom I just told so much of my life and who went to see some Detective. And I&apos;m... depressed even to think back. It&apos;s not about going to prison without a chance to get out, it&apos;s a point where your body and mind suffer so much pain you can&apos;t stand it anymore. It&apos;s beyond anything reasonable, anything that makes me remotely happy.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s raining. He picked me up later and drove me to his and Daniela&apos;s diner. It doesn&apos;t really matter what I eat... Josh gave me a burger, but I didn&apos;t eat much of it. Is it insane if you&apos;re hurt and enjoyed it... want more? I came here because things happened, but I can&apos;t really get rid of my old habits. I told Josh that I like being tied up, even as far so that I&apos;m unable to move anymore. It helps me to relax., forget about the world and concentrate on myself. He says I&apos;m not insane... just a lifestyle...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I told Josh a lot of things... just one evening where I told him so much although I wasn&apos;t really sure if I could trust him. He only told me one thing: &quot;I love you.&quot;&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans and Daniela know about it, of  course. Accept it, accept to be part of it and want to... I trust them, they trust me. Josh wants to be a part of it as well. I took the sweater off, showed Josh the collar. I base my life on what I believe in. It&apos;s what I want. I don&apos;t have the keys and can&apos;t get rid of it. Josh just kisses me, holds me, tells me how much he loves me and how everything makes a lot more sense now. Daniela is the most important person in my life as she has the key, it&apos;s the person who has all control over me. It&apos;s how I want my life to be and there&apos;s no way to get out of it. And now that Josh knows about it and wants to be with me even more... I doubt he&apos;ll just leave it as it is. He knows my whole life now, everything that&apos;s important to me. And he promised me he won&apos;t break it apart.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I can&apos;t really believe it... with Josh... I don&apos;t know what to say, I want someone to understand me but from what I knew of Josh before, I didn&apos;t expect it to be him. He just managed to become a part of my life... someone who understands and loves me... and someone I trust and... love. I want to be with Josh, but not only with him... just a lot. I can&apos;t be with Josh if Daniela doesn&apos;t allow it, she has the key to my collar, the key to my life. I trust her on making the right decision, it&apos;s  not mine. I want it to be this way and I want it to stay this way. It&apos;s all a part of my life and Josh understands it. Daniela took the key once to release the collar and all of my life fell apart, I didn&apos;t have anyone nor any reason to stay alive. I want to be with Hans, Daniela, Josh... I don&apos;t want to miss any of them.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;We left the Diner and went for his place in Palomino Creek. I still can&apos;t believe this happened... Josh wants it to happen again, every day of his life. So do I, but what comes with it is that at some point he has to take control and punish me for what I did. I want that. What if Josh had the key? I wouldn&apos;t know... but for now, I want Daniela to keep it. He picked me up and carried me into his bedroom, we lay down and were just kissing... Josh doesn&apos;t have to do something he doesn&apos;t want, it&apos;s all up to him. I ended up naked... and he spanks me, rubs me down there, kisses me, bites on my nipples, french kisses me, plays with my tongue, slaps my breasts, fingers me, tells me he understands me and would do anything to make me happy, fucks me, kisses me, hits me with his belt, stops.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;And asks when I&apos;ll tell Daniela.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I ask him to continue, almost beg him, didn&apos;t want it to stop... He taped my breasts together closely, put a vibrator in me and put some tape on there as well, then moved his penis to my mouth... stops when I reach an orgasm and swiftly rips both tapes off, moves the vibrator in and out, kisses me, tells me he loves me, takes it out, puts my clothes back on, kisses me, leaves to pick up Danielle... I&apos;m the only one Josh loves.</entry>
    <entry id="27" title="About what happened." date="November 18th, 2009">I need to talk with Hans and Daniela. I want to be honest with them, tell them what I feel. open myself about what happened. There are not much options. I could let them live with a lie, not tell them at all or just be honest. Honesty is the only way to go, I could lose their trust and that&apos;d be the least thing I want. I want to stay with them, but I also want to explore my feelings with Josh and frankly, I&apos;m still stunned after what was going on this night.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Called Hans, told him I need to talk as I&apos;m still quite confused. I asked him what he knows about Josh, only that he likes cars and works at SAN... nothing much. I think he fell in love with me, although he already has a girlfriend from the look of it. Still has her, I met her once when he introduced Danielle to me. I&apos;m quite unsure of what to think of this all. I don&apos;t know Josh that well but I told him about myself, Hans and Daniela. Why... I was drunk, down at Emerald Isle, he just picked me up and we&apos;ve talked a few words. I have some feelings for him as well, I believe...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans told me to try it, but... it&apos;s Josh, I wasn&apos;t really interested in him up &apos;till now. And then all of this, he talks to me, understands me, takes me home, and all is just... just awesome when I&apos;m around him. I want to share my life with him but at the same time I don&apos;t, I want to give up on Hans or Daniela... and quite frankly, I make it look like I&apos;m just about to. Hans is happy with whatever happens, he&apos;s happy if I am... But I don&apos;t want to lose any of them, want to stay with Hans, Daniela, Josh... Yeah, don&apos;t want to lose Josh either. I want to enjoy my life, only that... I love the time I&apos;m spending with Hans and Daniela and although Hans says it could be the time to move in... I don&apos;t know how I should go on. I want to keep the same kind of relationship and Hans pointed out we can always stay friends... and that I should follow my heart to know what I want to do.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I want to be with all of them, I don&apos;t want to decide for any of them on who to stay with, I love all of them, it&apos;s the people who make my life worthwhile. I told Hans that and he understands it... I want to continue, doesn&apos;t want to stop it if I don&apos;t want to. I don&apos;t really know what to do, I have no idea what I want to. Just want to live with Hans and Daniela for now, be with them, until I made my mind up and  hopefully with a decision that will make me happy.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I didn&apos;t tell Daniela yet. Didn&apos;t see her today. She&apos;s the person who might decide in the end, she&apos;s the most important person to me as she has the key, I don&apos;t know about Josh, don&apos;t know what to think of him, If I love him as well or if it&apos;s just something in my mind but not actually what I want. I was unsure about Daniela and Hans in the beginning but they wanted it to go on and so did I, I didn&apos;t need to decide because it was the only option I had. I need to tell Daniela, be open about it, I don&apos;t want to have to hide anything from her and even less something that could change my life so much.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He listened, won&apos;t kick me out, will be there for me... kissed me passionately. He gave me the feeling that everything will be alright and no matter what I decide on, it can&apos;t be that bad, I always have someone who cares.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans asked about my last name... I told him not to ask about it, I&apos;m only Natalie, nothing more... I want to have people calling me Natalie, Nat, Nats, anything like that, I don&apos;t want anyone to call me by my last name, don&apos;t plan on telling about it either, it&apos;s some leftover from Miami. My last name barely matters, I&apos;m fine with people calling me Natalie, it&apos;s on a more personal level and on one that doesn&apos;t let me think back.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans left, Daniela came.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;And asked me what&apos;s wrong, what&apos;s about Josh, if he hurt me. He did, but that&apos;s not the problem... I wanted it, I loved it, wanted him to hurt me, it just felt so good. Told her the story as well, on how he picked me up from Emerald Isle, drove me here and just talked with me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Talked about my life and I told him so much, he got me talking about things I&apos;m usually struggling to admit, or at least when I&apos;m with anyone besides Hans and Daniela who know about me better than anyone else. I didn&apos;t want to talk with Josh about it, or at least what I thought what was Josh. He invited me for Diner, I didn&apos;t really want to eat much... so we talked, and I showed him the collar, told him about everything with Hans and her. Josh knows everything, seems to understand it, to be okay with it, said he loves me. Took me to his house, it&apos;s obvious what happened.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Unexpected, but I guess we have to make it work right. I know it&apos;s my fault after all, I&apos;m sorry it happened. Daniela said it&apos;s going to work out, I shouldn&apos;t worry, but I have so many doubts. I used to live alone, then with Hans and her, no other place to go really. I had only two people to be with, they were together so there&apos;s not much to worry about. Josh and both of them aren&apos;t sharing a bit in common.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Should I make a decision or not? Should I decide on whom to be with even if Hans says it&apos;ll be alright? If there&apos;s one thing, this night confused me up to a point where I don&apos;t know what I want myself anymore. I don&apos;t know what to think, I don&apos;t know what to feel, I don&apos;t know if I should be happy I met Josh, mad at him for talking to me while drunk up to a point where I showed him my whole life...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;All he showed me is that he loves me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela is disappointed that I didn&apos;t ask her first, didn&apos;t ask her before I did anything like that. She has the key and I didn&apos;t let her know about any of it until it was already too late, but it&apos;s Josh and someone Daniela can trust and not some random stranger.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;m sorry it happened, I can&apos;t make it undone but I hope it&apos;ll be all good.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It all happened already and I have to work on from there. Everything is going to be alright.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I wish it&apos;ll end up like this. I can only talk about it, not wait until someone finds out behind my back leaving me no reason to explain what I think or feel.</entry>
    <entry id="28" title="Meeting everyone." date="November 19th, 2009">Stressed. Not looking good. Something just happened to my life and I don&apos;t know what to do anymore, what I want anymore. I want to enjoy my life... but whatever decision I make, it&apos;ll turn out bad, being a loss for the other side, losing the other side. I&apos;m afraid of what will happen. It was fine until Josh came in, Now... I feel lost in thousands of thoughts, lost in my feelings.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Miller needs some money, gave him a bit, 27 grand. It&apos;s not easy to solve my problem ,but it&apos;s easy to solve his... I wish mine was as easy to solve. Easy to solve some problems. Complicated to solve others. Either Josh or Daniela. Who is it going to be? Do I need to decide? Can&apos;t I have both? Maybe I&apos;ll get fired, maybe I&apos;ll end up beaten somewhere, I haven&apos;t got the slightest clue. What to do if all options are bad for the other person. I don&apos;t want to give up on anyone, don&apos;t want to lose either, keep them in my life and see them tied up, tying me up as well. Nothing much I can do but to think about what I want.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s just a decision that&apos;ll influence the rest of my life. I don&apos;t want to make the wrong one.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Thinking of a decision that&apos;s impossible to make. Choosing either of them. I&apos;m afraid what will happen if I do. That&apos;s just somewhat I feel I&apos;m forced to do. I don&apos;t know if I can have both at once. Can&apos;t believe I reached a point like this. I want all of them and have no idea how. I want to get an answer to the question on how my future will look, if I can still be tied up with Hans and Daniela around, can&apos;t find an answer. I&apos;m lost.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Until yesterday, Josh hasn&apos;t really meant anything to me. It&apos;s just all of this, just now... I didn&apos;t expect it to be like this,  didn&apos;t expect Josh to be like this. I want to be happy and all three of them make me happy. Daniela said that if Josh made me think so much on just one day, just a few hours, maybe the right option is in front of me, waiting for me, holding out a hand I&apos;m just ignoring, not ready to take, refusing to take because I want to stay with Hans and Daniela.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s all up to me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t want to choose. I feel like I&apos;m forced to. Maybe I shouldn&apos;t choose. Talk with everyone.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Went to talk with everyone at the Diner. Scared of what might happen. Scared of my future. I&apos;m not ready for it, want everything to stay like this. Explained the decision I feel I have to make... Daniela has Hans, who do I have? No-one? Josh? Hans and Daniela? All?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans asked about Danielle. She&apos;s out of town, Josh isn&apos;t together with her anymore but wants to be with me instead.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t have to make a decision. We&apos;ve set up a rule, one. Josh won&apos;t touch Daniela. He lived with that rule up to now, everyone else is fine as well. Hans doesn&apos;t really look convinced of it, looks quite opposed to like it, has a bad feeling about it... Getting married with Daniela, it feels awkward to him. Was good until now and he agreed just to see me and Daniela happy. Josh won&apos;t take her away, it&apos;s just a simple rule that shouldn&apos;t be broken, we trust each other enough. If he breaks it, I don&apos;t want to see him again. It&apos;s all based on trust and if that trust is abused... the same thing as in Miami isn&apos;t too far away. It always causes troubles.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I wish I could forget.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I have a great life ahead of me.</entry>
    <entry id="29" title="Random." date="November 20th, 2009">Met Josh, he&apos;s about to open up a car rental in Jefferson, just a block north of my house on the parking lot. Rent them to people, not sure if it works but you never know until you try. Installed a few GPS units, as soon as the cars are overdue they&apos;re sending their location and he&apos;ll get a tow truck to pick them up. Quite a couple of cars, not plenty but reasonable to start off small. Hope there&apos;ll be some customers, Josh seems to be quite excited about it. Ate a few cereals with him... went out.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s impossible to find a nightclub, one with a few people inside at least.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;We went to the Diner again. I don&apos;t have much time, so we had to make the best out of it. Kissing, getting rid of my sweater, kissing again, twisting my nipples and playing with my tongue, licking on my breasts, love him, letting me enjoy the time I have, letting me forget about all troubles around me, letting me forget about everything bad that happened, all the things in my mind...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Slept below four hours.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Went to SAN and found DeShaun sleeping on a couch. He ran here. Said he was camping with Josh and Daniela, at least until Daniela went inside the Journey for a moment and Josh pushed them off a mountain. Told me it should be no problem to make a decision now though I don&apos;t have to make one anymore. I&apos;ve settled everything, there&apos;s nothing left to discuss. DeShaun hopes it wasn&apos;t the wrong decision to make, I hope so as well. Nothing prove me wrong up to now. I shouldn&apos;t allow him to let me doubt Josh that much.</entry>
    <entry id="30" title="Danielle?" date="November 22nd, 2009">How&apos;s Nat&apos;s today? Tired... Had 3 hours of sleep. I don&apos;t sleep well lately. I&apos;m not over the things that happened in Miami, I&apos;m still scared of thinking back. Don&apos;t like to think back, to be all honest, I hate it. I&apos;m even more afraid the same thing will happen again, wherever it is inevitable, wherever it is bound to happen, I wouldn&apos;t know. Slept about 3 or 4 hours for a couple of days now. It&apos;s not healthy, I know. I&apos;m tired, afraid to sleep, know I&apos;ll wake up because I&apos;m dreaming of what happened.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve been writing some stuff here, collecting some thoughts, expressing what I have in mind, all that... I didn&apos;t write it for anyone but myself, I wish someone would read it, understand how I feel...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans called. Didn&apos;t eat anything today, so he asked me out. What do I want to eat? I wasn&apos;t aware of the fact I want to eat anything, probably have to, look at my health and all that. Something that wouldn&apos;t run away is probably not the worst choice. I don&apos;t like fast food, I would rather eat some better place, some restaurant...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Haven&apos;t met anyone this weekend until now, strange feeling to be all on your own...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He told me about Danielle. Josh said she moved out of town, left to Las Venturas, but Hans saw her at a bridge about to jump off. Why? Because Josh left her, because Josh kicked her out of his house, just after we had the discussion at the Diner. I was at Josh&apos;s place once, didn&apos;t see her around... And apparently, Josh had a car crash, something serious to make him stay in All Saint&apos;s General Hospital. Not serious enough to call me or let me know, yet Danielle was there holding his hand.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I told him of what DeShaun told me about their camping trip. I don&apos;t know what to think of all of that... Throwing people off cliffs, still being with Danielle? That&apos;s not the Josh I know, not a person I want to know... I thought he left Danielle for me, told me I&apos;m the only person he loves just in that very night we spent together. He made me feel good ever since that night.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I have to talk to Josh, see what happened. Though, can I trust him? I want to, I&apos;d miss him... I don&apos;t want to lie to him, but I&apos;m afraid of what will happen if I ask. Don&apos;t know him that good, but heard a lot of bad things about him recently... Should I just break up? Get rid of him, out of my life? I don&apos;t know what I want to - I don&apos;t want to have anyone around I can&apos;t trust, but I would miss him... I need to talk to clear up that one question that&apos;s bothering me so much: Can I trust him?</entry>
    <entry id="31" title="A perfectly ruined Date." date="November 22nd, 2009">I simply had to talk with Josh. I&apos;m feeling not that comfortable like this, it&apos;s quite bad to have doubts about him in my mind, I want to find out what&apos;s true and what&apos;s a lie. Asked him if he still wants to ask me out for dinner and not surprisingly, his answer was always.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What would I like to eat? Doesn&apos;t really matter, as long as I can sit with him, look at him, talk with him.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Danielle apparently left town and came back, it shouldn&apos;t matter much, all that matters is that he loves me and finally quit with Danielle. Some tattoo DeShaun claimed as Yakuza symbol was just a leftover from some surgery and how DeShaun was pretending to had a gun on him and was to accidentally shoot Josh and how it wasn&apos;t a cliff but a 6 foot drop.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Josh was arrested before, trying to sell guns to someone. The Police Department were going to size his properties if he didn&apos;t agree to supply them information on gun dealers. He accepted the offer and helped them, did what they asked for and now the story with this Niaki guy is over. He lives his life apart from them, doesn&apos;t on any weapons...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t know what to think of it, I really don&apos;t know. Nothing of this has to matter. All of this is the past and not the present nor the future.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Some of it happened today. Holding hands with Danielle. I have no idea how he&apos;ll go on with her but he told me he didn&apos;t love her, wouldn&apos;t have asked me out for a date in the first place. If he loved her, he would&apos;ve broken up with her and wouldn&apos;t be here in this room, here with me. I want to be happy and don&apos;t know if I can be that with Josh... He promised me he&apos;ll do anything to make me happy. That would be great... I can only wait and see if it happens that way. I wish it would.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Josh bought a limo last night, with the back seats folding into a bed and wants it to show to me. Picked the car up and went to lay down a little in the bed, apparently it has a couple of toys. It&apos;s not for the car rental, just for his own entertainment. Maybe we should go for some entertainment, demonstrate some of the capabilities of what can be done in here. There&apos;s a box with toys but I could care less about what&apos;s inside. I just lay down on my back, asking Josh to do whatever he likes. It ended up with me losing my pants, and a vibrator as well, bit licking here and there...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The car got lifted up, at least the front of it. Josh left me there and walked outside, didn&apos;t come back but we drove off. He sent me a message of how Hans towed it because it was parked wrongly. The car was lowered to the ground again and I got out just to see Hans. I walked up with him to the lobby and met Josh again, can&apos;t say I&apos;m enjoying the situation much. Hans drove with us, so there wasn&apos;t much options left to do. Asking him to leave would be somewhat unfriendly and after all that hassle... we ended up home and I walked in, decided to write a few words while talking to Hans. He&apos;s just working one day a week nowadays, must be my bad luck for it to be today. Hans left, I fell asleep in the office, my laptop still open...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Woke up an hour later, took my laptop - with closed lid for no reason - with me and the notes I have, on what I need to write about. I should go to sleep again, it&apos;s not been one of my better days. There is still stuff left to do, but that can wait until tomorrow. I would rather spend some time of sleep than on my blog and all those notes just now... I&apos;m just tired and maybe I&apos;m imagining it. I asked Hans and he said he just closed the lid, but didn&apos;t look at it. There&apos;s stuff I wouldn&apos;t want everyone to see, secret things shouldn&apos;t be widely known. Guess it wouldn&apos;t matter as much if it was Hans... I trust him. I&apos;m somewhat getting back on track with Josh again.</entry>
    <entry id="32" title="Maccer." date="November 23rd, 2009">Woke up to a clock showing 04:39. Not the best time to wake up when you&apos;re looking when I went to bed. Can&apos;t sleep anymore. I&apos;ve been dreaming of Miami, there&apos;s no way I could go back to that. I stood up and started walking around town a bit, just a small walk in this dull morning, fog everywhere I can see, it&apos;s depressing, the people look similar to the weather, whoever is up at this time has to have a damn good reason. I&apos;m struggling with finding some sleep, others could be walking home from a club. The streets are almost empty, it&apos;s hard to meet people. Nobody would go out with this weather just for the sake of being outside. Bought a bottle of vodka along the way. It&apos;s feeling cold outside, cold down here, nothing compared to the place I live in.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;As I walked down at Idlewood, not the gas station this time, I met this guy, Maccer Davidson. He introduced himself, told me it&apos;s the sector he is to govern and looking at the houses, it&apos;s an area I wouldn&apos;t have the slightest interest to live in. Didn&apos;t want to be annoying but I asked him to drive me home and he agreed, looking at how I was a little drunk he just commented he&apos;s doing the same for his co-workers.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;How is it, to loose the election another time? He&apos;s unsure about candidating a third time despite his two losses so far, he didn&apos;t say no at least. He&apos;s working for Malcolm Everett now and hopes to get a promotion to vice mayor. For one who has lost that&apos;s quite some expectations. I walked inside and showed him the place a bit, it&apos;s easy to show off here, a lot better than my own house in Jefferson. Not sure if I want to have friends by showing them where I live, but it&apos;s not exactly under the bridge of the freeway intersection.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;We have a recording studio for SAN usage, and although we have some guitars and I&apos;m playing much in this house, it&apos; no actual music. Has an own office, even SAN have pretty good offices now that Trave Construction finished their work at the interior. It&apos;s a huge place, enough to live in with a few friends. Maccer told me about his girlfriend and how she disappeared over night, it&apos;s not that good. I disappeared in Miami just over night and none of the people I knew has an idea of where I am, at least that&apos;s what I hope for, wish for, don&apos;t want them to know what happened to me. I came here to change my life, to get rid of the people I knew, to start fresh. There&apos;s always reasons to leave a place and if you couldn&apos;t trust your friends anymore it&apos;s time to search for other friends. If they know your life well enough and eventually abuse you, it&apos;s time to go somewhere else, being almost beaten to death isn&apos;t an invitation to stay. I left on my birthday since I didn&apos;t want to be around those kind of people anymore and with Hans, Daniela and Josh I believe I found true friends, people I can trust. I brought one thing with me, one thing that means so much and that I can&apos;t and don&apos;t want to get rid of, the collar. I don&apos;t have the key anymore, but I have a few selected people I trust, three people at all.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What&apos;s better? Calling a lot of people your friends or actually have a few you can rely on? I&apos;m open to meet new people I can trust, I&apos;m open as much as I can be. I want to be honest with the people that deserve to know the truth about everything, but who can I trust? Who cares about me? Not the majority of people I know, I thought I could trust people easily but it&apos;s not that way anymore. I can&apos;t just go on and give my full trust to anyone who wants to be my friend, not now. It&apos;s almost impossible to do when you&apos;re lucky you&apos;re still alive. If this is ever going to repeat itself, I&apos;ll be dead. Dreams aren&apos;t just dreams. They show what we want and what we&apos;re afraid of. Just now with Josh I&apos;m dreaming about Miami. The last thing I&apos;m waiting for, though I don&apos;t think of it as much when Josh is around, it seems to fade out a bit, leaving me to focus on other things. Two of those whom I trust live in this place. I would hate to ever tell them a lie.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The collar... It&apos;s about what I want my life to be. I don&apos;t mind a little pain, I can take it up to a point, enjoy it. You can go far beyond that to a time when all I want is to die just there... I had the... pleasure... to be at that point, I didn&apos;t enjoy it, hated it, was left alone, lost my life. I don&apos;t need the mansion to be happy, I want myself and the people around me to live a great life, an enjoyable life with doing whatever they&apos;re interested in, to feel happy. I&apos;m walking on my path, living the way of life I chose. It&apos;s not all about what I have, I may have to suffer for a bit to reach my goals and that&apos;s okay, everything is as long as I have some friends I can rely on and to help me for it not to get out of control.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t plan on running away any time soon. Up to now, I like it around here. Life ain&apos;t easy, my life ain&apos;t easy, but talking about it with someone is helping to a certain extent. Nobody needs to agree with all parts of my life, or any part of it, but it&apos;s my life and I won&apos;t force anyone to live it, won&apos;t force anyone into doing things they don&apos;t like. I&apos;d personally hate to do that, it happened to me when I wasn&apos;t asked if I agreed. I&apos;m on my way back to a normal life, recovering from what I have the bad luck to call my past. Trying to sleep through the nights without waking up...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I wasn&apos;t ever at the beach but I drove down there with Maccer, took a few steps in the sand, looked out at the sea. Walked along the beach, dropped him off at the Police Department.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Went home, trying to write a few things on my laptop but fell asleep... It&apos;s easier for everyone but me, I put myself into a bed and just hope to fall asleep at a point...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;When I woke up, Maccer was sitting next to me, telling me how he walked in through the garage. Came to see who&apos;s here. Breaking in... Maybe he should ask next time if he wants to come over and not just try to find any way. With all the kidnappings happening to Daniela, anyone could have went ahead and done that to me. Went back to the office and looked at my laptop. Glanced over at the clock saying 11:55 before I slowly drifted to sleep again.</entry>
    <entry id="33" title="Waking up." date="November 23rd, 2009">Hans woke me up and it&apos;s 12:11. Slept less than 20 minutes, that&apos;s almost amazing. I&apos;m close to four hours today, I&apos;ve slept less in the past few days. I know it&apos;s not good, I&apos;m tired all the time but when I&apos;m going to bed it just makes me want to stay up. I&apos;m afraid of sleeping and I know I&apos;ll wake up not too long after. I know what I&apos;ll dream of this night, next night and the night after but it doesn&apos;t make me happy.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;My dreams are about... me. What I want to forget, Miami. I ran away from the place but can&apos;t forget about it. It has to do with the collar. Everything has. It&apos;s a part of my life for four years now. I made the mistake to trust people I shouldn&apos;t have. Tricked into agreeing to something I shouldn&apos;t have, saying about how it&apos;s all safe and nothing bad will happen. It ended up wrong, just wrong for me. It took me a week or two before I could even move, sit or sleep without feeling the physical pain in my body. Who should I have talked to? The people I&apos;ve trusted all this time just showed me that all I had was worth nothing. I&apos;m afraid my time back there will catch up with me... that someone will find me... and take me away from what I have, ruin what I have... and that yet again the same thing is bound to happen... It&apos;s not only about me but also the people who are around me, that&apos;s the least thing I want. I don&apos;t want anything to happen to them.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans asks if I trust him, I nod without any hesitation. I trust him with everything I have, with my life. There&apos;s no signs this was the wrong thing to do.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;m afraid that the thing I want will break me down. I can take pain, want it up to a point, stand it up to a point beyond that but when it&apos;s pushed further... all I wanted was to die. Tried to cry, shout for help, couldn&apos;t... I didn&apos;t die. They didn&apos;t stop. Everything faded out eventually, everything went black, I collapsed... I don&apos;t know what happened afterwards, when I gazed around I had nothing, left there trashed behind in an alley behind a few containers with nothing left. Nobody was there to care for me, nobody there to trust in.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;No matter how much you mess up something, the only thing I&apos;m asking for is to care, make sure it&apos;ll be a bit better, letting the person know she&apos;s not alone and has friends who&apos;d do everything, help them recover from that situation. Nobody offered me a hand, I was given nothing. I was left alone. Nobody to talk to, no point in talking with anyone.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I know a situation can go beyond my control, but it&apos;s not half as bad as when I don&apos;t have anyone I can trust and who cares for me. Hans promised me to never abuse my trust, be there, help me...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;When I close my eyes, I see their faces, all the time... until I wake up. I don&apos;t want to sleep. I know I have to, but what does it help. I&apos;m afraid of it. It&apos;s easier for anyone who didn&apos;t experience it, wasn&apos;t there, only hears what happened. I don&apos;t want anyone to experience it... There&apos;s no way to reverse it, it happened... nobody can make it undone. I want to get over it. Forget it... when I&apos;m around with Hans... Daniela... Josh.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I still want the same way of life, bondage playing such an important role in it... just with different people, people I can trust. It&apos;s my way of living, it&apos;s not easy to change. It doesn&apos;t look like I want to change... I tried another way of life for a few weeks and got nowhere near happiness, it felt worse than what I&apos;m having now.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I walked up to my room, Hans followed me... stayed with me... Last thing I saw was 13:22 and then nothing...</entry>
    <entry id="34" title="With Hans at the Beach." date="November 23rd, 2009">15:41. I woke up again, looked at my walls and decided to get up. Just laying there wouldn&apos;t help me much. Went over to SAN to see who&apos;s there or if it&apos;s nobody as usual and to my surprise, I met someone, Akira Aizawa, about to go on air. I walked back to my cubicle and sat down in my chair. Closed my eyes for a while, tried to relax a bit, started writing again until Hans eventually found me... Just writing a few words down, stuff I&apos;ve been thinking about and that&apos;s going through my mind. I don&apos;t have to remember all of it if I write it down here, yet I can look what happened in my life, look back at it, be proud of it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The only one who works here is Akira, everyone else is outside, enjoying their day... I&apos;m just working here on my blog, Akira on his broadcast and Hans... is just here all the time. Maybe there&apos;s more than the office which&apos;s keeping him interested in going here. Not Daniela, he didn&apos;t see her for a few days. Me neither, though calling her over the phone would help, to make sure she&apos;s alright. Hans tried it, just a dead line for him. She&apos;s usually available when I&apos;m trying to call her. He suggested to report her as missing, though she&apos;ll come back eventually. I picked up a sandwich I brought with me, stared down at it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I showed Hans that note once, &quot;Thanks for letting me see my true feelings.&quot; He wasn&apos;t mad. I never understood why... I asked him, he had mixed feeling, was more disappointed in Daniela, the fact she didn&apos;t tell him honestly. What can I say, she told me she arranged a meeting with Hans earlier that day. He would probably have reacted in a different way if he knew before. Though, Daniela never lied to him about it, she just didn&apos;t say a word... Honesty is just a thing you can&apos;t go around, without all that there&apos;s nothing to build a future on. I&apos;m honest about myself, telling people what&apos;s in my mind and what I think might be important in my future life. Not my last name. Hans isn&apos;t disappointed in her anymore, it&apos;s okay for him now Daniela told him and he agreed with it, he&apos;s a left without clueless on why she couldn&apos;t discuss it with him though.... Well, can&apos;t help it but it hasn&apos;t been quite a good start. It hasn&apos;t been a great first time seeing each other, I really thought he could&apos;ve killed me in that car back then, at least I would have understood if he was raging, yet he was pretty calm.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I can&apos;t sleep here nor anywhere else and my interest in food is roughly as good as my sleeping times, thus I left the sandwich for Akira. A hard worker, who can sleep just as fine in our office rooms. There&apos;s not really a reason to stay here anymore, I&apos;m done writing another entry, and I&apos;ve talked with Hans a little about the next one. We&apos;re heading down to the beach... I can see it from my office, I have been there this morning.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Got rid of my shoes and walked around in the sand and the water... My office&apos;s view is lovable, it&apos;s a lot better down here. Took the sweater and jeans off and walked into the water, to swim a round or two. It&apos;s pretty fresh, almost cold. Couldn&apos;t stay in that long so I went back to the beach with Hans again, to lay down on the sand and to enjoy the view. I like spending time with Hans, at least he is a friend who is helping me a lot and is around pretty often. Just been laying there, doing nothing, close to Hans, enjoying my evening, watching the sunset, relaxing, feeling him close to me, helping me, doing what I enjoy...</entry>
    <entry id="35" title="A Talk with Hans and a Rope between my Legs." date="November 24th, 2009">Had a broadcast with Tom from Emerald Isle. Almost fell asleep so I pretended to have one of those important meetings you can&apos;t miss. It&apos;s 04:33, barely a time to be up. I left the studio, the only natural thing to do in that case and met a photographer with a Hawaiian shirt, stuttering all the time. He took a picture of me, blamed it on his new camera. Sat a bit in front of my desk, or rather had my head laying on it, slowly drifting off to sleep... Another flash, this guy is the only one around... I wonder what he&apos;s doing here, if it&apos;s anything else but taking pictures of me... He refused to show me the pictures on his camera, told me he didn&apos;t make any pictures, told me he was just leaving to get some snaps of the LSPD in action and even though it barely takes a minute to transfer those zero pictures to my PC... Told me it&apos;s just a few pictures of his first day at work, just of the folk around here, there&apos;s no one else around here. &quot;Accidentally&quot; took another picture. He wants to walk off to the bathroom, still not giving me the camera. I don&apos;t need anyone to take pictures of myself, yet him looking at the stairs when I suggest all of those pictures are of me shows it pretty clearly that I&apos;m not wrong. He ran off...  I&apos;d be happy if the biggest problem I had right now was that guy and not me barely eating or sleeping.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I went home, Maccer called. Still early in the morning, told him I&apos;m tired and in fact, I am, that&apos;s not even a lie. I&apos;m laying in my bed just now, trying to get a few hours of sleep. Two and a half, before I went to Emerald Isle again. Jimmy C was there, just as every so often, told him about my troubles with sleeping until Hans walked in. Early bird drinkers, it&apos;s not that funny for me. Wrote a bit for my blog, about the day Daniela broke my life apart and brought it back... thinking of what I did in so much time... It takes a while to build up a life but it only takes an instance to break it apart. I&apos;ve learned that in Miami. That was the worst thing that happened in my life so far.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The thing is that at the same time, I&apos;m not sure if it was the worst thing that could have happened... maybe I liked it to some extent, just a tiny bit... I don&apos;t want it again. I&apos;ve learned it here... that&apos;s been quite bad, but at least it went back to a state I&apos;m happy about... Maybe it was different if they were there for me, no matter how bad the situation was for me... That&apos;s what I&apos;m afraid of... that I want it... That&apos;s why I&apos;m thinking of it... I can take some pain... sometimes I want it... sometimes I like it... sometimes I deserve it... There&apos;s so many feelings  you can have at one time... so many things to influence your mind... Pain is one of them... and I want to explore my feelings, all of them. I&apos;ve lost control of myself already just because my mind couldn&apos;t take what happened around me... with me... any longer. But that doesn&apos;t necessarily make it bad, it adds something to it. Something to hate... enjoy... I don&apos;t know. I don&apos;t think it matters as long as I can be with someone to trust, someone who doesn&apos;t give up on me. Just someone who is there and holds me, takes cares of me when I can&apos;t do it myself anymore. I want to explore my feelings and my body, and sometimes you have to step over the line of what you think are your limits. Sometimes it was helpful, sometimes I stepped back. But I&apos;m only learning, and trying to make something out of my life, something I can enjoy. And I enjoy being with Hans, Josh and Daniela.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;... And now, I&apos;m just writing down the impressions I have collected, I can look at what I&apos;ve done in the past. Of course, trying to avoid similar mistakes in the future. Giving other people the control helps me to relax, enjoy and collect impressions. It&apos;s something I want. I know not everyone agrees to what I think. Most people think I&apos;m weird, just for the collar alone. Not a lot of people know me, barely a few whom I can trust...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I want to feel... pain... up to some extent, not as much, but some of it is okay. If I can trust Hans with that, I can always tell him to stop. If I can&apos;t... there&apos;s no way to get out of it for me. But I trust him... and whatever happens, if either of us is unsure, the best choice is to talk about it...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans admitted he&apos;s still feeling something for me, loves me... and that his life turned into something better when he met me and accepted me as part of his life. I&apos;m probably different from all the people he knew before, brought something different inn his life, and his life changed quite a bit because of that... And then again, Hans and Daniela wanted to show me their life, the life they enjoy and what freedom is for them. I haven&apos;t adopted anything from it, not sure if they ever tried to convince me after they put the collar back on. I think I&apos;m quite a bad learner at those points. I&apos;m still living my life, only theirs changed quite a bit... and they like it. I offered them another view of life, I left them the choice, I&apos;m not forcing my life on anyone. I&apos;m happy they put the collar around my neck again and took the key. I know I can&apos;t take it off now even if I wanted to... but I don&apos;t want to, it&apos;s something that reminds me of both of them. I&apos;m happy... or maybe proud... when I feel it around my neck, it does never allow me to forget what my life is and who&apos;s important in it. I can&apos;t lose it... I&apos;m happy when I think of it and I want them to be happy as well.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It shows my way of life and what I want it to be.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;m happy Hans is around just now, I don&apos;t have to worry about what happens or what happened... He thinks about selling BT&amp;amp;R, he doubled the company&apos;s value and feels like he did his job there... Maybe he&apos;ll come to SAN, then all of the people I trust work there. I&apos;m still looking at the entry I wanted to write, it&apos;s called Nobody wants my Life. Seems things have changed a lot. Shut down my laptop and drove home.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I was laying down on the couch a little, watching Akira&apos;s show... Hans came eventually, I&apos;m surprised he wasn&apos;t fired yet for doing no work at all. He took my pants off, handcuffed me behind my back, tied some rope to my collar, then ran it down over my stomach to my crotch and eventually tied it to the handcuffs on my back. Hans told me he&apos;ll meet me in my room and walked off. I tried to follow him, struggling quite much as I felt the rope rubbing my more private areas with every step I took, had to sit down for a while just after I walked up the stairs, I believe it wasn&apos;t too hard to hear me moaning. Got up after a minute or two and continued walking to my room, the rope is quite distracting. Looked at him, he asked me a few questions and I tried not to move my neck at all. Eventually dropped myself on the bed and started making out with Hans, I loved and hated that rope so much... he played with the rope, played with me, that&apos;s what I wanted, took a vibrator and slid it in and out, blindfolded me with his shirt and eventually made me silent by sticking his penis in my mouth, then took both out and fucked me, uncuffed me, untied the rope, kissed me until I fell asleep.</entry>
    <entry id="36" title="A wedding with Josh?" date="November 25th, 2009">Josh told me over Radio he&apos;s going to close the car rental and rather changes it to a Security Company... Same location and stuff, different vehicles. I&apos;m not really all that great, just woke up after sleeping three hours... I didn&apos;t sleep more than that every day this week. Three, four hours, that&apos;s it. He offered to take me somewhere north in his limo, somewhere relaxing. It&apos;s better than just laying around here doing nothing, there&apos;s a hope for exchanging a few words, maybe a hope for even more than that. I&apos;m at home, he picked me up... Our destination is a surprise.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;m tired, looking that way as well, I guess. It&apos;s not that I haven&apos;t been sleeping, just three hours ain&apos;t enough, you&apos;re supposed to sleep for eight hours and I&apos;m not even at half that... it doesn&apos;t help me a lot. I don&apos;t want to sleep, it&apos;ll be the same last night, this night, next night... I&apos;ve told him what I dream about, it doesn&apos;t make me happy, it&apos;s a challenge not to think about it and when I&apos;m just doing that I feel no happiness in my life. It happened, I can&apos;t change it. I trusted my friends and got almost beaten to death... I&apos;ve myself to blame, partially at least since I initially agreed, got tricked into doing something I shouldn&apos;t have done and I wouldn&apos;t have done if I knew how it turned out. Nobody would&apos;ve done it. I trusted my friends for years. It took ages to build up that kind of trust, or what I thought was trust. It took an instance to break it apart. I came here to forget about it, all of it, but instead I keep thinking of it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Josh said I&apos;m with him now and I should keep in mind I don&apos;t have to think about it. He took a box from the glove box, opened it showing a Diamond ring, saying &quot;Marry me, Natalie&quot;.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The time I spend is different from the time with anyone else. I really enjoy it. I was a little afraid of what he would do at some time. But I don&apos;t need to worry, he showed me I was wrong and he just gives me something I don&apos;t want to miss. I wish I had something to give to Josh that showed him how much I felt for him... I don&apos;t have the key, I can&apos;t give it to him but if I had it, I would... I wish I could...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I ran away from the people I couldn&apos;t trust anymore, that&apos;s the worst part, not that I couldn&apos;t sit, move, sleep for a week or two without pain... but that I couldn&apos;t trust them anymore, it went beyond everything I wanted to happen and I lost everything I had. All my friends, almost my life. I&apos;ve tried to find something better and when I look in Josh&apos;s eyes, it seems it worked...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;We&apos;re going back to Los Santos, and Josh told me I&apos;ll go to sleep, thinking about getting married and not about anything else. I want to sleep even less now, I want to be with him... I fell asleep in his arms and woke up later, carried to his house in Palomino to sleep, and did so yet again just in a bed and not the back seat of a limo...</entry>
    <entry id="37" title="Doubts." date="November 25th, 2009">Daniela called, apparently Josh told her about our plans for the future... our wedding, all that. I don&apos;t mind, I&apos;m done with sleep just now, a few hours, few more than usual. She asked how this happened, it seems to be just a week since I met Josh. I didn&apos;t prefer talking to her over the phone and asked Daniela if she could come down to Josh&apos;s house in Palomino.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She agreed and came here just ten minutes later. I&apos;m still tired, yet smiling... Asked if Josh was the person I&apos;d want to be with. Daniela has Hans, they&apos;re planning to get married as well and I want to be happy as well. She claims it to be unexpected just because it happened so fast. Though I met Josh on the day I met Daniela, the one night that even got me anywhere close to her. Guess my whole life is just a bunch of surprises or as Daniela put it, a series of shocking events, one thing following the other. First the way I met Josh at all, now I&apos;m getting married. I see Daniela and Hans happy and the one thing that certainly means something to me is that I won&apos;t marry Josh if Daniela doesn&apos;t agree. She didn&apos;t say she doesn&apos;t want me getting married to Josh though the way she tried to bring it across implied it. She is the person who has the key and it means something to me... I want Josh to have the key on our wedding and every day after that. It&apos;s important to me to get the key with Daniela wanting to give it away, I wouldn&apos;t want it for my own but only for Josh.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I trust her, Hans and Josh and I&apos;m not quite sure what the problem is going to be. Does it make that much of a difference? I know she thought I&apos;d always stay with them, with Daniela but it was me who started to involve new people... Josh in particular, and now I&apos;m getting married. If she does the same with Hans, that means she moves a bit away from me as well. I won&apos;t leave them, that&apos;s not my intention. I want to stay with all of them... all I wanted is to stay with them, but Daniela is going to get married to Hans and she should be happy with him... Does that mean I can&apos;t be together with Josh even if it makes me happy... I&apos;m not just looking around, trying to find someone to take me away.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela is talking about her wedding all the time, planning it, even setting a date for it. But that means she&apos;ll spend the rest of her life together with Hans and I don&apos;t know where my place would be there. I don&apos;t know what I should do... I love her, she gives me a feeling I&apos;m welcome but looking at it, she wants to be together with Hans... Maybe it&apos;s just my impression, but she claims it&apos;s quite different from that and that she really loves me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;If I marry Josh, I&apos;ll lose Daniela. And neither of us wants that. Maybe I shouldn&apos;t marry Josh but be with her... When I think of the wedding it feels like I&apos;m giving up a part of my life and of my freedom. Maybe I&apos;m not ready for it. It has been only a week. I know I said yes when Josh asked me, though I&apos;d rather want to stay with Daniela... I want to be happy and she does that, Hans does that and... Josh does that. Daniela and Hans, me and Josh. I&apos;m afraid it&apos;ll change to a point where we&apos;ve grown apart. Wanted to play a bit with her but she just pushed my hands away, just wants to sleep saying it&apos;s not the time for it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;That&apos;s what I didn&apos;t want to happen but it seems it already happened. All of what I thought could last forever is slowly falling apart.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I went to bed again and got up, been doing some work for SAN and met Hans. I told him about Josh proposing. Him and Daniela, it doesn&apos;t feel like there&apos;s a place for me, it doesn&apos;t feel right and now with Josh asking me, even less... I know I said yes, I want to be with him as well and I&apos;m quite in fear of the moment right now, to admit how I feel. In the end, I&apos;ll decide for Hans and Daniela. I didn&apos;t want it that soon. When either of us marries it&apos;ll take a part of my life away, one that I really enjoyed. Of course there never has to change anything... but that&apos;s not how it&apos;s going to be, it&apos;s just a feeling it&apos;ll be different that&apos;s hard to describe. I guess I&apos;ll tell Josh I don&apos;t want to, need some time. I tried to avoid this... and now I&apos;m in it, just as I told him already and... I have to make the decision, the answer is Hans and Daniela, the people I spent so much time with and the people I feel gave me so much more in my life.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What would Hans do in my situation? He doesn&apos;t know. I don&apos;t know. Nobody knows. I&apos;m not ready for what&apos;s going to happen, don&apos;t want it...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I went to the office and eventually decided to call Josh to tell him about it. I don&apos;t want to lose him neither do I hate him. I still love him but when he asks me the question of whom I&apos;d stay with, he wouldn&apos;t be the answer. He said it&apos;s okay if I&apos;m not ready and that I haven&apos;t lost him, that he&apos;ll always be there for me. I feel like I&apos;m disappointing him and he makes me happy, wants to make me happy even if that means something different for him.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela came to the office later and I made her aware of my decision. We went up the roof and saw some smoke coming up from City Hall, Miller told us over the radio there&apos;s a shoot-on-sight announcement and I&apos;m sure as heck not coming anywhere close. Daniela demanded me to go in the Helicopter and report about it... I told her I&apos;m not in the mood for it. She only told me personal lives will not have any influence on our job at SAN... and that she&apos;s sorry but needs me to report on it. If that&apos;s how it has to be, I&apos;ve quite too much things in my life going on right now and if I have to do that report when I work for SAN - That&apos;s it, I&apos;m out, leaving just here and now. I threw my keycard to the ground and walked off. Daniela offered me to take the day off but that&apos;s not quite much what I want right now. I don&apos;t want her to bug me at all.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;She has the key but what does that mean? She&apos;s right; I shouldn&apos;t have my life have an influence on my job. If I can&apos;t manage that, then I shouldn&apos;t be in that job. She ordered me to pick the keycard up and take the day off... It&apos;s an order, not something to discuss. She doesn&apos;t allow me to leave so I have not much choice but to follow that order.</entry>
    <entry id="38" title="Maccer&apos;s Death." date="November 26th, 2009">Maccer called me when I woke up and asked me if I&apos;m alright although he isn&apos;t himself and if I enjoyed the last trip to the beach. Of course I did and he tells me someone offered him a good and low price beach house and that he wants to give it to me, as a gift. I want to see it and he picked me up and took me down there...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s quite big house and I like it... Maccer thinks it&apos;s worth giving it to me and that it&apos;s worth spending time with me and I hoped he&apos;d say that. He offered me some coffee and he agreed... It eventually ended with me... being naked and all he did was jus&apos; to lay down on me and eventually having sex with me... Not quite the thing I had in mind and I wasn&apos;t too happy about it, he couldn&apos;t take his eyes off me and it lead to a thing I regret for ever allowing him to do it. It&apos;s a great house but... It&apos;s not worth this. I guess I just had to do something so there we are...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I offered him to play a game. He agreed and I put a hand on his eyes, told him to close them and he did. I put a finger on his lips and he went quiet. I put my hands on his shoulder and pushes it a bit down, leading him to move to the end of the couch and eventually to kneel down on the ground. I tied my sweater around his head to make sure he&apos;ll barely notice of anything I&apos;ll do. I took his hands and moved them to his back, he didn&apos;t resist but allowed it to happen. I took a pair of handcuffs I&apos;m casually taking with me. Told him to relax and just let it happen as I locked the cuffs on his back. After doing that it was my duty to some extent to convince him I had no key with me and that he wouldn&apos;t get free without them.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I took a bottle of vodka and a knife from the kitchen, put it against his stomach and let him guess what it was, eventually poured some of it in his mouth. He left his mouth barely open, ready to shut it any time but this is going nowhere. I haven&apos;t exactly thought of how it will happen but I&apos;m quite sure of one thing, it will. I put a gag in Maccer&apos;s mouth, something that helps him drinking and leaves him not quite a lot choice to refuse any more vodka. I locked the gag behind his head and took a flower vase, filled some water in it and let the water drop into Maccer&apos;s mouth.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He tried to get away and almost getting on his feet, he managed to fall on the ground. I sat on his back and started to tickle him, asking where he wants to go, left him not a lot to speak for still wearing the gag, still tickling him. I stopped and took the knife, moved the edge along on Maccer&apos;s body and started cutting some small lines along it. I asked him if he enjoys this and he didn&apos;t answer at all, not even nodding or shaking his head. I put the knife against his throat just to let him feel it, asked him again. He nodded.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;If I&apos;m asking a question, I expect an answer in an instant. I asked him what he&apos;ll do about this situation because right now, he could just report me. He shook his head but I haven&apos;t planned on letting him leave. I unlocked the gag and took it out, leaving him a way to express himself. He still loves me... Doesn&apos;t understand himself, but still does. Didn&apos;t enjoy the situation as much as he expected but he spent some time with me and said it was quite fun. Fun? What could I have done better except to leave him alive after it&apos;s all over? Maccer wants to have it more fun for himself as well and he blames it on himself for having a first time into bondage at all. He can&apos;t see, can barely move... It doesn&apos;t sound like he took it all that well. Truth to be told, that&apos;s not what I wanted anyway. He was afraid from alcohol poisoning in that drinking game... I&apos;ve thought about it but decided against it. He could&apos;ve passed out, died...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I pulled him up and took the sweater off him, pulled it over my head and put my jeans on as well. Walked with him through the front door. It rains. Nobody is out at the beach at this weather... that&apos;s the thing Maccer was afraid of, someone seeing him. Not his death. Walked up the water and told him I&apos;ve buried the key somewhere in the sand, not sure of the exact spot. It&apos;s looking different now. He wouldn&apos;t mind spending some more time with me, helping me to find the keys as long as he does that with me. I pretended it might be in the water but I can&apos;t leave Maccer here too long, someone will eventually come here.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Put the knife to his throat and told him to walk ahead, straight ahead in the water. Continued telling me he loves me and asked if we ever do it again, maybe with the roles being switched... If he wants that, we could surely do this another time. There won&apos;t be another time. I don&apos;t mind either side of it. He asked me if I was an escape artist once but for all I know I&apos;m a radio moderator. Just because escape artists are into this kind of stuff it doesn&apos;t mean I&apos;m one, if you&apos;re into this kind of stuff you just have to love it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Maccer is afraid he isn&apos;t coming back alive from his time swimming here and he only wants to look at me for a last time, I declined that. Told him he&apos;ll come back, he shouldn&apos;t worry but just go ahead. He loves me no matter what and promised me to keep this game a secret and I pretended I&apos;ll do the same, even when he&apos;s in control of me. Why would I tell this to anyone? I wouldn&apos;t want to harm his reputation neither do I want him to turn around and catch a glimpse of myself.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;If this game ends, that means he won&apos;t see me any time soon. Once he swims back ashore he wants to meet me again. Nobody said I won&apos;t be there, I&apos;ll always be there for him if I ever meet him again. The last things he asked me was &quot;See you on the other side?&quot;, of course... if it ever comes to that. He wants to hold me right now... I&apos;ll miss him. And put the knife through his throat.</entry>
    <entry id="39" title="911." date="November 26th, 2009">Threw the knife in the water and ran up to SAN and took a new van here. Hans called and wants to know how I am. Feeling good would be a lie, it&apos;s quite miserable. There&apos;s not much that makes me feel quite better just now, I&apos;ve told him I&apos;ll call him back.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It stopped raining. Called 911 to get some unit dispatched to the beach. Made a broadcast about it, just a few words... Had an officer coming here together with a cadet. Besides they spent a lot of their time driving through the sand to ruin possible clues, it must&apos;ve been looking weird to see Maccer there, his throat cut through, handcuffed behind his back.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;This story is a lie. I didn&apos;t come here to enjoy the sun at the beach yet it really rained all morning. I see this guy him, even more I put him here but that&apos;s not a part of what I told them. They figured it was murder, not a rather challenging task to find out. While they were busy playing hide and seek with all the evidence, together with the tide getting higher there wasn&apos;t much to do. I cried, Hans hugged me, we took some photos of it for the newspaper. Never bothered writing an article for it. A politician, a popular figure who&apos;s been seen with illegal guns. Wouldn&apos;t surprise me if he had some enemies who wanted to kill him. Nobody did it. They continued searching and Han picked up the knife from the water I just threw there five minutes ago. There&apos;s no CCTV cameras anywhere near and his fingerprints are on it, so are mine. Finding footprints is a rather non-trivial challenge looking how the police officers drove almost in the water to be close to him.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Time to be sorry. I am. If I had the choice now, maybe he wouldn&apos;t have died. There&apos;s always only a choice and no definite answer. Choice. Freedom. I used the choice and if it comes back to me, my freedom is taken away so is my choice. I don&apos;t want to have too much choice. It helps me focusing on the area accessible to me.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Mr. Thompson wanted to ask me a few questions about what happened. How would I know, I killed him but officially I was the one who just came here for a sunbath. My name. Natalie is my artist name, just about how everyone calls me and how everyone knows me. Nobody knows my real name, I never allowed anyone to know in this town. He needs my contact details because I might be called later about the investigation, every single bit could help. Every single piece can help to solve the puzzle but it&apos;s no puzzle for me, I know all the pieces, I know the murderer and what happened, I know more about the person in question than anyone else. I don&apos;t want them to solve the puzzle, I can&apos;t throw pieces at them. Mr. Thompson said I&apos;m not in any trouble. I&apos;m lucky not everyone knows. Natalie isn&apos;t my real name, not the name I have written on my driver&apos;s license, not anything like that. Nobody checked it so far but now it&apos;s impossible to withhold this information.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Nicole Westman.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans is confused and I can understand that... I didn&apos;t want to be called by my old name anymore when I moved here and... I still don&apos;t want. He knows what happened, I told him. I&apos;ve asked Mr. Thompson if he can keep me updated as it&apos;s my job but the only thing this is useful for is to find out how far they are connecting the pieces. It&apos;s my job to report about it but even more it&apos;s my interest to deny any useful information for them.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The cadet found a dead fish they&apos;re going to examine, nothing to do with the case. Why would I tell them... every trace that leads the Police wrong is a step on my way to get out of this. A brief statement, yet again. Came here to enjoy the morning, saw him... and later, called 911. Didn&apos;t see anyone besides me around, people avoid the beach when it rains. I left while it was raining and - that&apos;s even true - came here right after it stopped raining. I don&apos;t need to be told how helpful I was, how appreciated the conversation with me was because after all, it wasn&apos;t any help to me. Mr. Thompson offered victim support for me, talking about traumatic things along this some may need help with. I&apos;ve had an interview or two with Maccer, knew him a bit, and now to see him end like this...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;SAN gets you in contact with people even more than you think. People want to contact you, that&apos;s great. None of them tries to get anywhere close on a personal level though. Maccer tried and failed, I didn&apos;t allow it to happen in the most extreme way possible - death. Mr. Thompson knows it&apos;s a tough time for me yet he&apos;s not aware of the full level of details. I shouldn&apos;t think of it too much. With the information I gave them, he said, they&apos;re hopefully able to catch the guy... I&apos;d be glad if they catch the guy, indeed. Not the girl, because that&apos;d be me.</entry>
    <entry id="40" title="What goes up..." date="November 26th, 2009">Hans took me right away from there to the SAN tower, went to the coffee machine and brought two cups of coffee with him. Sugar and Milk were the parts I had to add manually, it&apos;s not easy nowadays to completely rely on others to do anything... even have to do the killing yourself nowadays, ha-ha. It&apos;s not funny. Not even a tiny bit.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The story I told at the beach was close to be a lie, contained some truths but I avoided talking about a lot of things. With every lie, with everything you hide comes doubt. I&apos;m trying to be as open as possible because when I&apos;m not, others doubt me, I&apos;m unhappy about it because there&apos;s a chance I might accidentally tell it to someone else and it&apos;s avoidable just by being open to the people you call your friends. It&apos;s not about being open to everyone but have people to talk to. If you don&apos;t it&apos;s...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I did not tell Hans my full name, not even my real first name. Why should you trust anyone if you can&apos;t even trust them with their name? I never claimed it to be an artist name or fake name or any of that kind yet I only called myself and let others call myself that way. He doubts my trust because I didn&apos;t tell either... he won&apos;t bite my head off, won&apos;t do anything but just continue calling me Natalie. Why didn&apos;t I tell him? What&apos;s the difference if I do or not, I don&apos;t want anyone to know me by my name. I came here and forget about everything that happened. I&apos;m partially afraid to meet someone from my past but what concerns me even more is the memories that come back when I hear my name. Natalie is just something new, a new name with no memories attached to it... and I want everyone to know me by that name. I&apos;m sorry I didn&apos;t tell Hans, maybe I should have done it... I just do not ever want to be called by that name... just Natalie is enough. The name doesn&apos;t make a difference, it&apos;s the person that matters...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It was me, I killed Maccer and I admitted that to Hans. I used the knife on him... Why? It just happened, just some kind of a stupid mistake. He wanted more of me, wanted to have me all for him alone, called me in the middle of the night... I didn&apos;t want it, didn&apos;t share those kind of feelings up to the point he wanted me to and I couldn&apos;t really accept this. It just went down this way... I wasn&apos;t really aware of what I did. Hans doesn&apos;t want to lose me, he cried. It was just one time, a big mistake. I know it&apos;s my fault and I shouldn&apos;t have done it, even more regret it but it&apos;s too late for it now. He has to decide how he wants to go on with me, it&apos;s all up to him and I want Hans to decide on whatever is right.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I went up to the roof and sat down just on the edge, my feet swinging freely, looking down. It wasn&apos;t a busy day, barely any traffic, barely anything going on down there, just my live changing up here. He loves me and doesn&apos;t want to have anything to happen to me...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;What if the police finds out? I don&apos;t know and I didn&apos;t think about all of this, it just happened... I&apos;m not exactly sure on wherever I should tell them and unfortunately, nobody can help me with that, nobody knows... Looking down makes me realize how easy it is to end a life. It certainly is easier to end your own than to end other people&apos;s lives. I&apos;ve caused so much trouble to Hans, Daniela, everyone... It&apos;s a beautiful view over the beach up here and although Maccer&apos;s has been taken to the morgue already, I know where it went down... The sea is calm now that the rain is over, the sun shines, nothing of it all reflects myself, my thoughts, my feelings, my doubts, my life. I&apos;ve jumped into a situation without a way left to leave easily. The easiest way out would be to leave. Hans doesn&apos;t want me to.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I need to leave SAN as well. There&apos;s a no crime rule. If you commit a crime, you&apos;re out. Hans suggested nobody to know of it but with all there is to it, I&apos;ve tried to hide my name from him and I felt miserable when he finally found out. I don&apos;t want the same to happen yet again. Nobody in this town knows my name, now I can only say nobody should know it. He wasn&apos;t amazed after all. All I ever wanted to be is honest... but I even lied to myself.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ll turn myself in. There&apos;s no other way. I&apos;m not proud of what I did. I regret it but it is what I did no matter what everyone says. I don&apos;t want to live with yet another lie...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Miss me... Hans loves me and will miss me... I will report myself and I hope he&apos;ll be happy with Daniela, hope Josh will be happy but what is there left for me? How can I be happy? What else should I do? So many questions I cannot answer. Hans can&apos;t either, nor would I expect a reply from anyone else. I made mistakes in my life, a massive one just now and I shouldn&apos;t run away from what happens to me all the time... He couldn&apos;t keep this for himself either... I love him as well and I can&apos;t imagine a life without him or Daniela, Josh...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;One of our last moments together and I can&apos;t change it. It happened no matter how much I didn&apos;t want it to happen or how much I regret it. I just wanted to be happy with Hans, Daniela Josh and even if I&apos;ll always be in their heart... I can&apos;t be with them. There&apos;s two options... Wait for the police or just... jump... The only thing I could ask for is him to visit me from time to time, there is nothing I could even demand in the slightest way.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Mr. Paris went up on the roof... I hope Hans&apos; life ends up better than mine, that he&apos;ll be happy with Daniela and visit me from time to time. I miss him now already and I&apos;m still here, haven&apos;t said anything negative yet...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t want Hans to think bad of me... I didn&apos;t want anything bad to happen...</entry>
    <entry id="41" title="... must come down." date="November 26th, 2009">I walked down the stairs with Hans and Mr. Paris and left the SAN tower... What goes up must come down, here I am, more down than any time before since I arrived in Los Santos. Kissed Hans, asked him for the ID back... He wanted to come with me to the PD at least but I&apos;m not the person to ask that... Went to the Los Santos Police Department.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He couldn&apos;t enter the office with me. I didn&apos;t want that but it happened and... I have to take whatever consequences there are. I could barely manage to look him in the eyes, just kissed him again... Walked in the office while he waited outside. I&apos;ve told him about my past, the reasons I left, my family, my friends, whatever I had there and what all meant nothing to me. My name was just a part of it, one of the things I got back there and I don&apos;t want to have. I&apos;ve chosen another name, Natalie. Nobody in Los Santos knows my last name nor my real first name except for the two Police Officers I met in the morning and Hans.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve shown him the pictures I took with my digital camera, Maccer after he died. Told Mr. Paris about him, that I&apos;ve seen him a couple of times and what I felt about him, that he wanted more than I wanted... what I felt for him... I was just laying on the couch in that house and he undressed himself, jumped on me. I&apos;m not really clear what happened afterwards or... I have no urge to talk about it. I lost control over the situation and I do know what I did. I won&apos;t deny it, there&apos;s no point to. Although he might be a bad guy at times I didn&apos;t want it to happen to him. I regret it, but that&apos;s not what matters... I made him walk to the beach, naked for the handcuffs. Put the knife to the throat, and he could guess what happened. It wasn&apos;t easy, I didn&apos;t want it and even if I did, this wouldn&apos;t be the place to admit it. Now that I&apos;ve done it, I won&apos;t run away from it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Mr. Paris asked if I&apos;ve been to the hospital and I really didn&apos;t have any time for that. I&apos;ve called the police after what happened roughly two hours ago, told them what happened but not that I was the one who killed him. Walked up to the SAN tower to think about all of this. I&apos;ve thrown my life away in just a instance when all I wanted is the whole thing with Maccer to end. It ended but not as I wanted it to turn out. I couldn&apos;t help but cry, didn&apos;t want to see him dead.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;There&apos;s no death penalties in San Andreas so it&apos;s most likely prison for life. It&apos;s up to the judge if I might get out in 20, 40 or 60 years. What&apos;s the point in it if I wasted 20 years of my life for nothing? I&apos;m 21. I won&apos;t know anyone. Nobody will know me. Mr. Paris told me I wouldn&apos;t waste my life and though I&apos;ve seen a lot of bad things that&apos;s not the only thing to it, good things have happened and that I seemed quite happy on the radio shows. I won&apos;t be on radio anymore. SAN has a no crime rule, even if I got permission to do a show from jail I can&apos;t continue working there... What do I have in prison? Nothing. What do I have when I come out? Nothing. Maybe it&apos;s an experience, maybe it&apos;s pleasant. I made some experiences I wish I never made. I&apos;m afraid to sleep because I dream of them, wake up after a few hours and I&apos;m at about three hours of sleep per day because of a single experience. It won&apos;t change, I won&apos;t be able to sleep really.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Just a few formalities left to clear... I&apos;m officially living at 11 Belview Road though I haven&apos;t been there for a while. My only car, the Euros I got from Hans and Daniela is parked at their house... The Cadet who was there earlier came in for a moment and was asked to bring the evidence. I only have three friends in this town, Josh, Hans, Daniela, none of them is related to this. The Cadet came again with the thing he was asked for, why&apos;d they need it... I confessed and the fingerprints on the knife will be mine, everything will point to me. More evidence... some nurse came and did a few things...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Mr. Paris eventually came back, took a photo of me and told me to remove any heavy objects. The only really heavy thing I&apos;m wearing is the collar but I can&apos;t take it off. Daniela has the key and I&apos;d rather keep it, but it&apos;s not possible and they need a firefighter to remove it. I just fell to the ground, left there crying. It&apos;s the only thing I want to keep... I suggested asking Daniela for the keys, I&apos;m wearing it for four years now and I don&apos;t want it off but due to that being impossible, don&apos;t want it to get damaged... Hans got the key while Mr. Paris took my height.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Hans is sorry he has to do it, did it... but he had no choice. I cried even more as the only thing that&apos;d connect me to them in some way is gone. Mr. Paris took the collar as evidence though it&apos;s not related, I&apos;ll get it back after it&apos;s been processed to decide what to do with it. I told Hans to keep the key. It&apos;s not his fault. It&apos;s all mine. Got put on the scale to see how much my weight is, not that much of a surprise, it&apos;s not changing often.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Down as far as it can go. Cells. Hans can&apos;t follow inside. I have to take everything off me, even my clothes, all I was left with is a jumpsuit and a cell with a bed. I will stay here tonight, next night, the night after...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I see no light ahead of me. I see no life ahead of me. I&apos;m not up in SAN, in my life with the people I know, I&apos;m down here, left to rot within this cell.</entry>
    <entry id="42" title="Three walls, Iron." date="November 27th, 2009">Mr. Paris came. Opened the cell and told me I have a visitor. I&apos;m not in a rush, I have all the time I want. It was Hans, he told Daniela and Josh. It&apos;s unexpected... I didn&apos;t expect it either.... it just happened, but without wanting it that doesn&apos;t mean it didn&apos;t happen. They&apos;re missing me, that won&apos;t help me. I&apos;m out of SAN, I&apos;ve committed a crime and not only a small one. Then I don&apos;t have either of them around me. I&apos;m all alone and there&apos;s only myself to blame. A small present, a bottle of vodka, all that because they miss me. But if I ever come out of here, everything would be different. I&apos;ve killed someone and everyone knows it. It wouldn&apos;t be the same no matter how much I want it to be.&#x0A;&#x0A;What&apos;s the point in life if you don&apos;t have anything? What do I have? I don&apos;t have a job. I can&apos;t enjoy my life with either Hans, Daniela, Josh. I&apos;ll sit here forever. Seconds... Minutes... Hours... Days... Weeks... Months... Years... Nothing matters within my cell. What if they release me in twenty years? I&apos;m 21 now, what should I say? I spent half of my life doing nothing, have no jobs and no friends. I always loved Hans, Daniela, Josh but that one thing ruined my life, it&apos;ll never be the same. I just want it to end, it won&apos;t get any better. I begged Hans to help me, to spare me of a life like this, it&apos;s not one I can live. He denied it, loves me too much. It&apos;s hard to see for him that I&apos;ll just rot here, nothing but four walls and an iron door, a bed, that&apos;s all I&apos;ll see for the rest of my life. I didn&apos;t accept the vodka. Good Luck to him... with Daniela, to have a better life with her than I could ever have. Everything went too fast lately. Three weeks ago I literally rushed into their life and now I have an even quicker exit.&#x0A;&#x0A;I don&apos;t mind if Hans would lock me in a cage somewhere. I don&apos;t mind a lot of things, I just want my friends around, someone who cares, someone I want to be with. And all of this is taken away here. I don&apos;t want much, I only want to die. I wish I could be a part of his life. Mr. Paris came again. 8 minutes over the time, Hans had to leave. I refused to get up. What&apos;s the point in going back there. I&apos;ll just have a life without anything that makes my life worth living. I don&apos;t have anyone, anything. He didn&apos;t want to shoot me, asked if I wanted to live with hindering him from going on duty as well. I don&apos;t want to live at all. I fell back in my cell. Didn&apos;t get up, saw no point to.&#x0A;&#x0A;My life is reduced to this cell. There&apos;s no easy way out, not any way out at all. Nothing outside this cell exists. There&apos;s a couple of things existing in this cell, I can tell them on one hand, wall, wall, wall, iron door, bed. I exist but don&apos;t want to. I wish there was only five things to exist within this cell. Everything is dead but me. The walls, the iron door, the bed, nothing I can talk with. I&apos;m surrounded by dead objects. I want to be a dead object. It would take so many things off my shoulders, nobody would sue me for things I did, regardless wherever they were intentional or not. I couldn&apos;t regret. I couldn&apos;t love. I couldn&apos;t miss. I wouldn&apos;t get out of here either.&#x0A;&#x0A;Another officer came, I don&apos;t know his name. Asked for my name and if I killed someone. I wouldn&apos;t be sitting here if not. I don&apos;t like it here and I could care less if he comes back another time. I&apos;d rather kill myself than rot in this place for the rest of my life.&#x0A;&#x0A;Josh came. Knows what I did. Asked about the collar. I&apos;m not allowed to have it before court date. Josh doubts I&apos;ll get it back. I don&apos;t want him to have it. He wants me to promise him not to lose hope. There&apos;s nothing I could lose there. What can I hope for? I won&apos;t get out for the rest of my life. I don&apos;t have a record but how does that help me. I can&apos;t ever enjoy the time with him, Daniela, Hans again. I&apos;ve killed someone. Record doesn&apos;t matter. Maybe I&apos;ll get a few years off, I&apos;ll be 41. I&apos;ve wasted half of my life. Josh said he&apos;ll be waiting for me even at that age to marry me. I can&apos;t go back to SAN... Josh told me I don&apos;t have to but could run away with him, move to LS and become nudists. I can&apos;t run away. I&apos;m here. I&apos;ve turned myself in and I know what I&apos;m here for. After I get out? I&apos;m in for the rest of my life. Josh is angry because I keep saying that I won&apos;t get out. I wouldn&apos;t know yet. Maybe I don&apos;t. I already felt like I&apos;ve spend an eternity down there with nothing. I don&apos;t have no friends there and nothing to do.&#x0A;&#x0A;I have Josh... but he&apos;s not there. Just comes here from time to time. I know what I did was wrong and I&apos;ll take whatever I have to. What use is it if I get out in ages and can&apos;t spend any good time with Josh, enjoy my life. He has hope, tells me I should have hope as well. I&apos;ve been told the chances are slim, almost impossible. There&apos;s nothing else I can hope for. Josh cried, I cried, we kissed. That&apos;s all. The guy who brought me here wants me to tell him my side of the story again. I don&apos;t think it&apos;s necessary, I&apos;ll either talk to Mr. Paris or not at all. I&apos;m in custody though nobody read my rights, he claims to have the right to question me. I have the right to remain silent going by that, last time I checked at least. I have a cell to rot in, I don&apos;t want to waste my time with this.&#x0A;&#x0A;That guy sort of feels sorry for me, won&apos;t stop from asking me why I did it. Just a mistake that won&apos;t get me nowhere out of here. It&apos;s too late, I&apos;ll stay. Claimed Maccer would have ended here if he kept going like this. Now I&apos;m here. Food... Thanksgiving, who cares. I didn&apos;t touch the food.</entry>
    <entry id="43" title="More visitors." date="November 27th, 2009">Hours passed. Looked at the wall for any irregularities, just a slight difference in color, everything lost its color for me. The walls are white, the bed is white, the iron door is white, and outside is white. I&apos;m in the middle of an empty room, crying for my friends. There&apos;s the pictures, that&apos;s all I see besides the nothingness of the world around me, three faces I wish I could see every day, those of Hans, Daniela and Josh. I&apos;m tired but have no urge to sleep. Whatever I do in this cell has no influence on the outside world. I can&apos;t do anything but wait. I always said when being tied up the world revolves around me and I can&apos;t do much but watch if it is what the dominant part wishes or actively take part in changing it if I&apos;m given the opportunity to. That it was this is. Nothing outside is of any matter to my world. I&apos;m not given a chance to change it.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t think of the trial at all. I didn&apos;t sleep, I didn&apos;t eat. Does it matter? I&apos;m in no state to live healthy after all, it wouldn&apos;t matter how I feel, I can&apos;t convince a door to open by looking at it and being sick. Do I believe in live after death? Maccer did. Do I have faith in the lord? Barely. I don&apos;t believe in god and having a life after being in this cell - no matter if here or after death - would be a weird thing.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Another person visited me, Akira Aizawa, our only TV Show host. Told me the usual things on how I shouldn&apos;t lose hope. My friends will remember me in 20 years? I&apos;m 41 by then, old, ugly, missed my chance to stand out as a great person by killing someone. I&apos;m in doubt wherever I&apos;ll get out at all, yet he&apos;s the one telling me there won&apos;t be a life sentence. Slim chances are better than none. Hans was here, Josh was here, and even Akira was here… Yet the one who hasn&apos;t made it down here yet is Daniela. It&apos;ll all be over soon for me, one way or another. When he left he told me to stay strong, for what reason? There&apos;s nothing awaiting me, no future ahead of me. No matter if I&apos;m weak or strong, the walls don&apos;t care, the Iron door doesn&apos;t care, they are strong enough to hold me in against my will, being strong in here doesn&apos;t help me a tiny bit on the way of getting out. If there&apos;s a way for that. I&apos;m pretty much at the worst point already. It can&apos;t get worse, can it?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I had to go back to my cell. There&apos;s no newspaper or books, internet access, anything like that down here in the Los Santos Police Department. Mr. Paris tells me that once I&apos;ll go to the State Correction facility I might have a lot of things they can&apos;t provide here. He gave me a Gameboy with Pokémon Red and Yellow, something to do while I&apos;m only waiting for my trial. There&apos;s nothing in this cell, just a bed which I did not yet use.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The wall is all the same, brownish, pale, and white, nothing. Over hours, I&apos;ve tried to get rid of this cell I hate so much, just in my mind, thinking of something else. A white room with pictures of my friends, myself laying on the floor curled up and crying is the answer. I am pale, tired, watching nothing, seeing nothing and caring about nothing. No matter what I do, time to my trial will not pass any faster. When someone banged against my cell door with the night stick, I looked up to see Daniela. I don&apos;t think Natalie is doing all that good. She&apos;s pretty tired. And she&apos;s sorry she&apos;s such a disappointment for Daniela, anyone. I want to be Natalie but she doesn&apos;t exist in this cell, the most important thing taken away from her is the same as to take away me from myself. I have no reason to exist. I know I did something wrong, that&apos;s why I&apos;m here. I have no friends in here yet I want to be with them. And without friends, my life means nothing to me. Daniela just told me they&apos;ll be there forever. How long is forever? There are years to come, years to go, maybe a lifetime. It&apos;s not the same just seeing people, I want to feel them as well, want them to feel good when they&apos;re around me and not sad because I can&apos;t be with them, just looking through those bars.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It&apos;s too late for Natalie to do that, even to exist any further. Things have changed, maybe my friendship hasn&apos;t. It&apos;s too late to look back, everyone tells me to look ahead in the future but when I look there, there&apos;s no light to follow, just the darkness that&apos;s around me just now which I&apos;m trying to escape by burying Natalie deep within myself, trying to separate whom I want to be and whom I am, not letting both parts contact each other a lot. I don&apos;t want to stay here for the rest of my life. Maybe I should just… go to the other side. It&apos;s too late for me to go back.</entry>
    <entry id="44" title="Free." date="November 28th, 2009">56 hours down here, a world with only me, without any chance to get out. Nobody can help me now, can they? There&apos;s a trial waiting for me. I&apos;m not waiting for it, everyone&apos;s trying to make me look forwards but that&apos;s not the direction I want to go. I want to go back before this all happened, never let it happen, be happy with Hans, Daniela and Josh.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Michael Valentino came down to my cell; he&apos;s working for SAN. As other SAN employees already did before, the most noticeable one being Akira as I barely know once and couldn&apos;t call him a close friend, he came down to my cell. It&apos;s an evening, for sure, there&apos;s no reason to call it a good one. Wanted to ask, the usual story, met him, killed him, there&apos;s nothing on it ever changing. It happened, there&apos;s only my version of the story as nobody else knew him.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Michael offered me to get me out of here, I wouldn&apos;t know how. Of course, it&apos;d be great. Money doesn&apos;t mean much to me as long as I can get out of here, it&apos;s barely a matter of that but that I&apos;ve turned myself in and admitted killing him. I&apos;ve always been troublesome, attracting trouble like a magnet... I&apos;ve slept with Daniela and expected to at least get killed for it, but after all, this beats everything I&apos;ve done by far. Even worse that it was something being my fault, regardless of how much I wanted it before and how much I want it now. It fit the situation, but what kind of lame excuse is that?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He demanded the cadet near me to let me free, apparently Judge Archer has released me. My rights were not read. In fact, they weren&apos;t but that&apos;s nothing I would ever think of. Just a small, minor detail in all of this mess they call an investigation on me. Apparently Justice falls for that. I can&apos;t believe it myself. Paper work, that&apos;s always what&apos;s left to do before anything interesting may happen. That&apos;s the only thing that stops me from being free just now. Maybe it&apos;s a trick. Maybe it&apos;s real. I want to see the people I want to see or this all means nothing to me. I can&apos;t say how lucky I must&apos;ve been, but after all it&apos;s just amazing to turn out like this.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Still took a while, Mr. Valentino has been waiting outside, just me left down here...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;18:49 was the time I walked out of the Los Santos Police Department, free for now until they&apos;re all recovering from that great event and find a way to put me back. It&apos;s always the same, ain&apos;t it?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I had to get my stuff, my car, my personal belongings, whatever I lost in the process of being there. I told Mr. Valentino I&apos;ll give him a call later. The police impounded my Euros for once yet there&apos;s something more important I need to get. I went back in, had to. Mr. Paris was there, I couldn&apos;t hide a smile. He couldn&apos;t look me in the eyes but told me to have a good life, and I have hope in that. They don&apos;t have my car? I thought they impounded it but I might be wrong. My life is nowhere I want it to be, there&apos;s one thing I need to address as soon as possible. I&apos;ve called Josh to pick me up yet he can&apos;t help me with that, unfortunately he can&apos;t...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I told him I needed to go to Hans&apos; mansion... I know it was probably wrong in that situation but all my thoughts didn&apos;t contain my freedom, Josh or Hans. I called Daniela and told her I need to see her at my room, right now. Nothing else was needed as much as it. It&apos;s easy to describe the situation when Daniela went in. I&apos;ve been kneeling on the ground, naked. The collar was lying in front of me together with a pistol I bought. One bullet is enough for me. I&apos;ve been only looking at the collar, didn&apos;t look up when she came.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;There are two options on how to go on from here. One option would be to forgive me and put the collar back where it belongs, accept me back. If Daniela can&apos;t do that, the other option is right in front of me as well. It&apos;s not about what I want. It&apos;s not about what anyone wants. Only Daniela has to make the decision and tell me what she wants. I&apos;m not wanted, all charges were dropped. If she doesn&apos;t want me back that&apos;s all up to her. There&apos;s no option to see me alive without the collar. Either she puts it on me or I&apos;ll kill myself. I know there are other possibilities. I don&apos;t want another life.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Daniela picked up the collar and held it around my neck, wondering if I&apos;m absolutely sure if this is what I want. I am or I wouldn&apos;t kneel here like this otherwise. It&apos;s either that or nothing. She locked it and I fell in her arms, just being there to be held crying. They&apos;re here for me, it&apos;s going to be alright... even more, I am alright, I&apos;m just so happy I can have my life back. I&apos;ve told her what I did in cell – nothing to eat, no sleep at all... She got some food, hot dogs, not that I&apos;d mind anything right now.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I didn&apos;t tell Josh much before that, I wanted to see how my life will it go on – or more importantly, if it will. I&apos;m sorry for the whole mess, I&apos;ve disappointed her two times in two days, looking at the future makes me believe I have a great one ahead of me. I ate something, didn&apos;t care much about sleep, I wasn&apos;t tired.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I&apos;ve told Josh about being free, what happened... I shouldn&apos;t worry about my job, he&apos;s just glad I&apos;m back. Danielle is out there, standing in the grass, waving. She&apos;s following Josh everywhere... She&apos;s crying, probably because she knows Josh and Danielle won&apos;t be together in future, maybe she had some hope while I was in jail. She&apos;s not looking good, I don&apos;t want anyone to die but who am I to say that? Josh told me he&apos;s in love and proposed to me for that very reason yet he doesn&apos;t want Danielle to kill herself either. It&apos;s going to be okay for me, I hope it&apos;ll be okay for Danielle as well.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;We left Danielle there crying and went to Josh&apos;s place in Palomino Creek. I shouldn&apos;t look back, it doesn&apos;t help me. I&apos;ve learned from my mistakes, I won&apos;t mess up stuff again. We&apos;ve been laying down on the bed a bit, nothing much more. I wanted to get out of that cell so bad... to be with my friends... to be with him... I&apos;m just happy I still have the chance. All I wanted is to get out of there, no matter how... even if I had to kill myself. But here I am. Holding Josh, kissing Josh, promising me he&apos;ll never leave me, telling me he won&apos;t let me go...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Sleeping 9 hours...</entry>
    <entry id="45" title="Destination Unknown." date="November 28th, 2009">When I woke up, Josh was next to me, still holding me, smiling. He had some coffee ready and asked me if I want to move in with him. I was told to move in with Hans and Daniela so that&apos;s what I did. Apparently Daniela told Josh we can marry when we&apos;re both ready and that she&apos;s okay with it. I&apos;m not sure if I&apos;m ready for it. She probably won&apos;t mind me moving in here, I can still be with Hans and Daniela whenever I want, Josh&apos;s not trying to take me away from them but I know that.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I don&apos;t think it&apos;s yet the time. I&apos;ve been through so much in the past three days. I just want to slow down a bit, relax, sit back and enjoy my life. I&apos;m so happy I&apos;m still welcome here, nobody wants me to leave. There&apos;s a time for everything but I don&apos;t feel like planning everything right now. Just be happy with what I have right now, that&apos;s what I&apos;m thinking of. The future is lying ahead of me yet I&apos;m in no hurry. I have the rest of my life to do whatever I want. I&apos;m free and have a world to explore, I can actively decide on my future. Just cuddling against Josh is all I want right now. I&apos;m happy I can.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;The rest of my life follows no plan as I have none; I&apos;ll just live in the day and wait for the best to happen. My destination? Unknown. All I know is that it&apos;ll be with the people I love.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;It didn&apos;t take me long to fall asleep again.</entry>
    <entry id="46" title="Suicidal people." date="November 29th, 2009">I&apos;ve went to the Office, at least I haven&apos;t been fired yet, that&apos;s the good side. I possibly will, but right now I can just do my job as usual. Anchor at SAN, at least something I like. I&apos;ve got a call by Sergeant Hansson of the Los Santos Police Department, and luckily it wasn&apos;t even about me. He called about a situation at the Sherman Dam connecting Tierra Robada and Bone County. I took Kaze with me, I didn&apos;t want to go all alone and have nobody to talk to during hat drive. I let him drive, I was the Lead Anchor at least and he was just below me. None of us seemed fairly interested in the story and as nobody told us what it&apos;s about, there was nothing to be excited about just then. I started eating a salad during the drive and once we arrived there, still focused on that and set Kaze out to talk with them while I finished.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Apparently it&apos;s a worker of the Los Santos Emergency Services, called Gao Donghai, who&apos;s about to jump off. There&apos;s always people who want to kill them self, or at least threaten to, due to their interest to be on the news. He likes It up where he is, standing on a car to have a great view over the dam. Indeed, the view from up there it&apos;s great but it seems people take the “jumping into the scene” thing a little too literally.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;So much noise out there while I&apos;m just trying to eat. He has no friends, no place to live in, no car and just a job that pays not enough. Don&apos;t we all? Yet I paid my lawyer three millions. At some point, money doesn&apos;t matter anymore but I don&apos;t have any interest to throw it at people to let them have a life they can&apos;t handle. Kaze has no interest in saving Mr. Donghai, yet he better should do. None of us is paid for letting people jump and in our listener&apos;s interest it&apos;d be better to show people how much everyone around them cares and wants to help them. At least we should be trying to show them every life has something good...&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He wants to start private investigation company instead of working for the Los Santos Emergency Services. Now that&apos;s surely something more interesting yet it doesn&apos;t save lives. If everyone would do that, people would die all the time without getting any treatment. Looking at the prices of that, and that it only artificially keeps people alive who were yet to die, looking at the things they have to deal with sometimes isn&apos;t easy, but at least it helps a lot of people. He demands an office and a work car, can&apos;t use the Jester he apparently owns to chase criminals. Heck, if he wanted to chase criminals then maybe that&apos;s what he wants. Everyone should be able to work on their dreams and possibly realize them but threatening to jump if that doesn&apos;t happen? What pathetic people has this world.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Kaze suggested him to step back to be a star, just like everyone who wants to suicide, one of those people everyone laughs about because their life is just hopeless. Because they don&apos;t want people to help them until it&apos;s too late. I&apos;ve told him about how happy I was I didn&apos;t kill myself and how good my life is looking now. He demands a parachute, those about to die always demand things for free for the sake of their lives. Nobody had a parachute there and it wouldn&apos;t be high enough to skydive regardless.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;He jumped. Sergeant Hansson had an Interview with Kaze who was drinking the free drinks that were around the place and yawning a couple of times live on air. I couldn&apos;t blame him for it. People kill themselves every day, if we&apos;d report about it every time we could never go off air. Apparently there&apos;s been a series of suicide jumpers, maybe it&apos;s the fucked up economy in the place we live in, losing a lot of money might&apos;ve been the reason he came here. He refused to let anyone help him but talked about gangs and individuals to threaten him before his death, yet the Police Officers being with him in critical situations could not help him with that?&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;I drove back, drove to Kaze&apos;s mansion. He offered me a coffee, nothing more. We went out to his balcony, looking down at town. I&apos;ve told him about what happened to me. He was surprised I wanted to kill myself; I should&apos;ve had someone to break me out and pretend I got kidnapped. According him, the worst mistake I did was not to kill Maccer, killing isn&apos;t a mistake to him at all, and the only mistake I made was to turn myself in. I could&apos;ve never spent time in there and could&apos;ve carried on with my life without them knowing, Kaze says it&apos;s easy. I would always have something to hide; now that I&apos;m free I have nothing to worry about. I don&apos;t need to be afraid someone will find out what I&apos;ve done because everyone knows already. It could&apos;ve turned out wrong, pretty much so. It worked one time but not another time. I won&apos;t take the risk another time. He told me I shouldn&apos;t kill people myself but pay people to do so. I should think of them as associates as it&apos;d make things easier. But that&apos;s not the way I think about it, I won&apos;t be happy with anything else. Houses, cars, money, whatever else you could be happy with, it&apos;s nothing compared to the people I love.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Kaze is waiting for one of three groups of people to find him and kill him, has no options left yet he doesn&apos;t give up, he&apos;s still alive, he still has hope that it&apos;ll end up good. It&apos;s not a life I could imagine. No friends, no people to be with, all alone, waiting for your death.</entry>
</cache>
